What do we say to the god of dental hygiene?
Not today.
Because today is Friday!
Haha!
Mmm.
Oh yeah.
I mean, I can't change my whole life because of that one dentist.
God damn it, I did my best.
Sometimes you gotta crack open a cold one.
Hahaha!
Wait, what the fuck are you guys talking about?
Imagine joining the stream, seeing the streamer die, and everyone just says that was so deep.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, that would be funny, man.
If I ever die on stream, you'll have to say that.
Even though it's kind of sad.
Hahaha!
Funny you should talk about dental hygiene.
You are the dentist.
Hey, how'd it go?
Any cavities?
Float like gravity?
Got more family than the one in Scott?
No, got more rhymes than the one in Scott family.
God damn it, I can't even remember my tribe quest quotes.
Mmm.
Okay man, dude.
I am feeling it tonight.
I feel that noita power bubbling up inside of me.
Tonight is the night.
Replace the fallen out temporary, filling with a new one.
Oh, nice.
Okay, well, very good.
It has now been updated to the latest patch.
You're a senior now?
What do you mean?
My final year of...
Oh, when you said senior, I thought you meant like an old person, like 70, 80 years old.
I thought you were joking because of all of your birthdays, so that you were now 80 years old.
My mind went straight up the wrong way here.
I overthink things immediately for some reason.
It's weird.
Finally catching nights alive.
How you doing, ghost?
Been doing any flying lately?
You know, I've been doing some flying myself.
But in Microsoft Flight Simulator, I'm getting hyped for the new version of Flight Simulator 2024.
I know it's not real life like you, but I'm still getting hyped.
And yeah, I just think it's so cool that you're actually a pilot.
I keep thinking about that every time I see your name now, just so you know, you're like the pilot in my mind.
Any particular plans today?
The plan is to own.
Oh, man, I'm gonna be playing so well.
And you guys know, I'm not actually going for a win.
I haven't been going for a win since I got my win.
I'm going to... I'm going for a crazy build.
Lots of HP, lots of survivability, smart perks, smart choices.
Everything is smart, okay?
Smart watches, everything.
And then I'm gonna explore the world.
I want to go to the ancient laboratory.
If I can, I want to go to that new area that I discovered.
To the east of, I think it was the art, one of those places.
I marked it on my map, so I can always check.
I want to do all those things.
I have big plans, okay?
But those big plans may be cut short, because as some... as someone wise in chat once said, and I've... sorry, I can't remember who it was, but sometimes Noita giveth and sometimes Noita taketh away.
Let's just hope that the Noita gods are pleasant today.
We have to sacrifice stuff to the gods for them to be pleased.
First the astronaut, now the pilot.
Yeah, it's crazy.
Doing great.
Been busy.
We should do Microsoft flight simulator together one of these days.
Yeah, man.
Do you know anything about GA aircraft?
In particular, the A2A Comanche.
A2A is the company that made the Comanche.
It's a two-person... no, it's a four-person plane, I think.
That's the one I'm trying to learn right now.
I mean, just simple stuff, but I really want to learn it, you know?
Would be a lot of fun.
It could be like an instructor.
And yell at me when I crash the plane.
Happy Friday, everybody.
Gambler's Fallacy says that you should get a long run today.
Hmm, let me think about that.
Yeah, you're right.
You mean because I've lost so much, right?
Recently.
I had to think, what does Gambler's Fallacy mean again?
Oh, you're right.
That's the whole idea of, oh, I've lost so much.
Now I gotta win, you know?
But it's a Fallacy, so you know, I think Noita has all the right to be taken away and not giving anything.
So, yeah.
All right, guys.
Let's see here.
Change the scene.
Hold on.
I forgot how to stream.
Let me show you exactly what I meant.
I want to go to here.
I didn't mark it yet on the map because I need to know exactly the dimensions of it and all that.
And then I want to go here.
Those are the two big ones right now.
Also want to explore more of this place, even though it's kind of scary.
If I get the melee immunity, then I may venture in there.
But if I don't, I don't know about that, you know?
Then I also just kind of want to go this way.
I was over there once, exploring, but I didn't find much, but I kind of just want to try going there again.
Same this way.
In fact, I want to go down here.
In fact, I want to go up there.
I want to go all the places that's not currently marked on the map, damn it.
So this is a map, okay?
And you see how there's white lines on the map and there's blackness in the back?
Well, for you, it's transparent, but the idea is there.
Pretty much every spot that is not filled out, I assume there's something there.
You know?
I don't know if that's true or not, but we will explore it.
That's the plan.
Hold on a second.
Let me just see here.
Okay, yeah, that's the plan.
Back to here.
Okay, I will close you guys down.
Hold on.
Got to do that on my second monitor.
69 viewers!
Nice!
I love it, guys.
Keep it like that.
You're not allowed to enter or leave now.
I'll see you guys on the other side.
I may take a break at some point and talk to you guys just because I feel like I'm... I don't know.
As a streamer, I should talk to you more.
That's what streamers do, right?
In any case, new game.
This is my, I believe, 91st run I'm starting.
Almost at 100 runs!
Exciting stuff.
Let's see what we got.
All the energy sphere!
My favorite!
That's boating well, actually.
Hold on, let me get my drawing pad out of the way.
Let me see if I have enough real estate on my mouse pad.
I do?
Perfect.
Okay.
Also, I got to move these playing cards away.
I've been doing magic tricks again.
It's that time of the year where I sort of get completely absorbed in that.
I sit there and riffle cards all day.
Okay, there we go.
Everything is cleansed.
The table is ready.
The food is being cooked.
And I am deadly.
What's that?
Oh, hold the phone.
I know where I'm going.
Actually, do I know where I'm going?
Yes, I do.
Oh, we have, hold on.
We have three bombs?
That's gonna be a little troublesome.
So I was thinking in my mind, oh, I have levitation.
I can get to the top of the mountain.
Okay, but wait, no, I have these three bombs.
They're gonna roll down the hill so I can't get in.
Oh, but maybe I have enough bombs.
Oh, but maybe it's not enough.
So maybe I want to go grab a one that has some more explosives before I hit up.
That's what I went through on mine in that split second.
That's why I maybe seem so confused sometimes.
What the fuck is that?
Yo, that's some bullshit.
What the hell?
I can't even get to that.
Unless I use one of my precious bombs.
Okay.
Oh, there's always something below this.
Like I say it every time, but it's true.
It's true.
Whoa, that guy's a wand.
Oh, it's an arrow wand.
That's kind of shit.
But maybe it's okay.
I'll take it.
And then I'll bomb the shit out of this place.
What was in there?
I can't tell.
Also, I gotta get back into playing this game, man.
I think there was some kind of poison in there of some sort.
Or no, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, maybe something fell down.
A wand.
Oh, broken wand.
I see.
I will grab it because we need it later.
I'm actually so grateful I figured out what the whole broken wand situation is all about.
And I kind of figured that out early as well.
Like that shit has been serving me well.
Even though I feel like I've been a little unlucky with those.
Like they haven't been that great.
But maybe that's the norm.
Okay, let me go up here.
94 HP.
Okay, I will not lose any more HP in this whole stream.
This is gonna be a hitless run from now on.
Why am I... I can't even say that.
Of course, that'll never happen.
Would be nice though.
I mean, I just need to press the buttons in the right order at the right time and I will actually not lose any HP.
Think about that for a second.
That's how easy it is.
What's going on?
Oh, that's a chest.
That's a chest right there.
And that's wood.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm gonna do this.
Yes.
Lovely that.
Oh, they're all dying to the acid.
And guys, I know it's toxic sludge.
I call it acid.
I call everything green acid.
Don't add me.
Okay, let's water this.
Whoops.
Water.
Spells.
Unstable crystal with trigger.
I've never seen that.
That's cool.
Doesn't seem super useful though.
Makes a projectile decelerate acid.
Oh!
That would be really good on healing spells if I have to catch up to them and get hit by them myself.
That could come in handy.
Also, why am I?
I want to keep going here.
Yo, these things came out of nowhere.
What the hell?
Where'd you come from?
That was so weird.
I just cleansed that area.
Hello.
Gimme.
Hold on, did I remember to start recording?
I did.
I forgot to record last time as well.
So the latest VOD is actually in 1080p.
Again, because I'm a dumbass.
But now it is recording, so that's nice.
Okay, I'm gonna go right.
Two shots with the energy sphere.
Is it energy sphere or sphere?
Okay.
Wow!
Even more!
Sure.
I'll take it.
Also, I should grab more water.
Man, I want to get high today.
We're gonna be eating shrooms.
Can you feel it?
Something's happening there and makes me uncomfortable.
Some kind of physics issue.
Seems to be happening there.
That guy doesn't care.
Barney.
All right, I guess I gotta go all the way around.
I still have two bombs left.
I'm gonna save him.
Wait, what is this?
Oh.
Oh, I need the tablet.
We need the tablet, of course.
Oh, we need to get rid of... Let's leave one of them here.
Nice.
The tablet.
Oh, the tablet is so good.
So, there's a strategy I want to try against Stuart that I mentioned last time, but I never really got a chance to actually do it.
Which is like, I need to practice my tablet throwing skills.
And if I can consistently throw them in a specific manner with enough, like, momentum, maybe that's gonna be enough.
But it that's like the big if, or like the big requirement.
Otherwise, if I have to go pick up the tablet while he's fucking gunning me down, that's not happening.
Nope.
Definitely not.
Okay, well, we took care of the right side.
Still no hearts.
That makes me sad.
But it's just a fake kind of sad.
It's not real.
Because it is Friday and nothing can make me sad.
I'm fueled by that feeling.
I wonder if these markings mean anything.
Oh, there's also a wand.
Like, there's these little, um, I don't even know what to call them, altars of some sort.
Where the items are located on, right?
They always have some sort of writing.
Stillness, baby!
That's big.
That's a really good spell.
In fact, I'm gonna put that on my three because for some reason I always have that on three.
Boing!
Oh, hey, what?
All right.
Oh, he's still frozen like that.
That's funny.
Even in death.
Oh, I should have used my tablet there, of course.
I just remembered.
Did I see a haemus?
I think I may have.
Come on, man.
Show me hearts.
Sometimes I wonder, do they hide hearts in there?
Oh, but I can't really dig.
So, whatever.
Nice.
Come on, get the water over there.
300 gold?
Not bad.
Ah, let's not destroy this box yet.
We may need it.
Oh, it's boulder time.
Yes.
Wait, is he trapped?
He's freaking trapped.
I'm trapped!
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
I'm stuck.
I can't move.
Oh, kick the thing.
There we go.
I feel like that's karma right there, isn't it?
I should not be saying that stuff.
It's only going to bring bad luck.
Damn it all.
Why are there so many haemuses?
I mean, I don't, I don't, I don't mind.
It's money.
Hey, miss.
And then we have some kind of potion in there.
I can get in there, I think.
With this.
Actually, I can just go above here.
I'm going to do that.
Wait.
If I do this...
Like, right here should be enough to get rid of that, I think.
Oh, it's very close.
I'm not sure it's enough.
I can't fit.
Dang it.
Oh, there's a wand.
Oh, it's my wand.
I already forgot about that one.
Ah, I guess I'll go all the way above.
See if there's a way in.
Get rid of that.
Look at all the haemuses again.
This is the ultimate hemisphere.
At least on the haemus front.
Oh!
I need to pay attention where I'm walking.
I tend to look where my cursor is and not so much at my character.
I think that's not good for me.
Because I sometimes just walk into bad stuff, you know?
Because I'm looking... Oh, nice!
I'm looking where I'm aiming, which is, of course, something you need to do.
But I need to sort of switch back and forth with my eyes.
Make that a habit.
Oh my god.
The haemuses have gotten the best of me.
It's not looking good.
I'm just happy that I have my energy sphere.
You are dead.
Okay.
Sometimes the hearts are buried in coal and shit.
So whenever I have digging capabilities, I think I should always clear out coal piles.
Just in case.
Or like sometimes they're hidden in snow or something like that too.
Okay, there's nothing here.
But there's stuff up here.
Can I get up there?
Maybe through here.
It's crazy how different the game is when you don't have any real digging capabilities.
I mean, we have this box, I guess we could use.
And this.
And dead end.
Man, not many ones, huh?
I mean, we found a couple, but not really good ones.
Is this a bad idea?
Nothing here.
I could, you know what?
I'm gonna do this.
Shit, didn't even destroy anything.
All right, I guess I'm going back out.
I do still have two bombs.
Oh wait, I also have these.
I forgot about my firebolt.
Get out of there.
Let's not get hit by that.
Let's go through here.
Okay, I think the only place we haven't explored is down and left.
With this, I could go grab the heart on top of the mountain.
And I will.
Just after I'm done with this place.
I want... Oh, what's that?
Teleportation.
You know what?
I'm actually gonna...
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
It's in the teleportation.
That's kind of unfortunate.
Uh, shit.
I guess we can quickly do it.
Quickly!
Okay, the shitty one.
What?
Okay.
Uh, oh, I'm 58% on the... Oh no.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Okay, it's gone.
It's gone.
Always gotta be really careful.
Okay, so another thing.
I actually kind of need to pay attention to what the tooltip says.
Because I'm still wondering what the difference is between chaotic and non-chaotic teleportation.
Or like unstable, I guess.
Let me... I'm doing this for science.
Let me kill you first, just in case.
There we go.
Whoa.
You teleport uncontrollably every now and then.
Okay.
That sounds like the other type as well.
Man, what is the difference?
Okay, let's go here.
If I find unstable, I will look at the tooltip for that as well.
Oh, that's lava.
That is not good.
Hey, Hamis.
Oh.
He dropped two gold.
Okay, I think it's confirmed by now.
When you kick things on people, they drop more gold.
Accident.
It's gotta be what determines that.
Right?
It's gotta be.
That shit's been blowing my mind for so long.
I wonder if it works with my tablet.
Oh, uh...
Like, look!
Two gold?
Did you see that?
Two golds.
One, two.
Boom.
Confirmed.
Fucking that shit is put to bed.
Case closed.
Folder has been tucked away in the corner.
Never to be opened again.
I saw a guy here.
Oh, the frogs.
Whoa!
Hello.
Should I be using... Oh wait, I also have the freezing.
Shit.
I'm slippery AF.
What if I water this while there's toxic sludge in there?
I guess it's just gonna react with the toxic sludge, create more water, but the oil's gonna stay.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
God damn, I hate these.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Stop spraying on me, damn it.
I'm having a nice oil bath.
There were some frogs here as well.
Gotta be careful.
In fact, I'm gonna do that.
Just to protect myself.
Hey, froggy.
That's right, dude!
Dude, that circle of stillness is insane.
I think I may try to make a build with it.
Like, I just lure people into it and we're Gucci.
There we go.
Oh shit.
Oh no, he's throwing all kinds of bullshit.
Wait, I have tablet.
Tablet!
Oh sick!
The tablet collide mid-air.
He's kind of backing me into a corner here.
Got him.
Not bad.
Oh, sweet crits.
Polymorphine.
Nah.
Nope.
That's not good.
Don't like that.
Don't you shoot that.
Can I... does this produce light?
Oh shit.
Oh, I froze it.
I froze it.
Wait, why am I so stuck?
Oh, I can't see anything.
I guess I froze the ice, which makes sense.
I wonder if that's a way to actually get rid of the water.
If you just freeze everything and break it apart.
It's not just gonna produce water again, though.
Oh, what was that sound?
Uh-oh.
I heard a bad sound.
That sounded to me like a spell of some sort.
From up here?
Oh, that guy standing on dangerous terrain.
Phamoxium.
Oh yeah, look, there's someone being... I think?
Polymorph up there?
Oh yeah.
Watch this.
Oh, look at all the gold.
It totally works.
Incredible.
We have found a new way to farm some gold.
Proven method.
Oh my god, I'm actually dead.
Almost dead.
Maybe it's time to leave.
Oh, there's another frog.
I'm playing it really risky here.
I have a thousand gold.
You know what?
That should be an indicator to leave, I think.
Yeah, fuck it.
Let's go.
And with 18 HP, we pick up the heart immediately.
Yup.
I forgot to go to the mountain, but that's okay.
Okay, that's nice, actually.
Some of those and some...
okay.
What do we got?
Oh, I hate this thing right here.
Revenge explosion.
Oh, no.
See, all of these, I don't care about any of them.
I'm gonna reroll that.
Repelling cape.
More blood.
Oh, that would be really nice for vampirism.
I may just go with critical hits.
It's like just damage increase.
Straight up.
Okay, let's see.
Any good wants.
That's not bad.
Is... no, it's not bad.
This one is also kind of good.
Yeah.
Oh, this one is actually kind of sick.
Cast two spells at once, though, and has a long recharge time, so maybe not the best.
This one is also kind of good.
Damn, these ones are not fucking around.
I like it.
Triple scatter.
A double.
I kind of want to get this for the double.
Yeah, I'm getting it.
Get the light as well.
Honestly, just get all these.
What about...
I think I want this one for that spell.
Just because it's a good spell.
And then replace the shuffle wand.
Yeah, that wand is kind of shit.
There we go.
What is this one?
Right, the bomb.
The bomb.
Okay, what can we make with what we've got?
Let me see here, 0.15.
Sometimes just seeing it for myself is way better than just reading the stats.
I just need to get a feel for it, you know?
Okay, so it does that.
But maybe I would not like that.
Maybe I would rather have something else.
Wait, this one actually digs, but just a tiny amount.
Like, it sort of digs.
Oh, but it's way too slow.
That could work, I guess, in a pinch, but it's really bad.
It's not good.
I like that.
This is not going to do anything right.
No, okay.
We can put some light on it.
Make it look nice.
I want this.
And that's it.
I think I'm good.
That is all a man needs.
But 135 HP, that's really...
Not the greatest, huh?
Okay, so here's the thing.
I don't think we can kill the dude.
Unless circle of stillness.
So here's what I want to try.
He's going to spawn here, right?
Hold on, can I even anger him?
I don't even think I have the capability of angering him.
Never mind.
But I was going to do this, basically.
He's going to come like this every time.
He's got to come through here.
So if I just practice a throw.
Let's say I stand where this box is.
Something like that.
Or maybe I go up higher so that it has time to fall and gain some momentum.
Maybe I go like this.
Or maybe I wait.
No, hold on.
I stand like here and I go...
And then on the drop.
Oh, that's not bad.
That could work.
I'm going to try again.
On the drop.
Yeah, I guess that could be...
You could make that consistent.
And maybe combine it with circle of stillness.
I do not remember if I tried this on steward.
But, yeah.
Okay.
All this gold that I can't get to.
We got to find something to dig with.
It's actually kind of important.
Whoa!
Not bad.
Would love to have a chain bolt at this time.
Then again, this weapon is actually not bad.
This is solid.
Don't like the lava.
Maybe...
I want to try and adopt a new strategy for exploration.
Maybe I go all around the edges first and then I explore the center.
You know, like go left here and then I go down and then I go right and so on.
Also, what do I have?
I have...
Oh, wait.
I have the critical thing on.
That's right.
So, I do more damage.
On average, I guess.
Okay.
But, hold on.
I should use my tablet.
Get more money.
Fuck yeah.
Look at that.
Double the money.
I mean, it isn't...
This guy right here is an imposter.
So weird.
Oh, wait.
I can dig with this.
I completely forgot about that.
Oh, my God.
I guess I'll dig with that.
Wait.
Wait, why am I...
Come on.
There we go.
So much damn lava.
Look at all this mess.
What a disaster.
I want...
Dude, I need berserkium right now.
That will make digging easier.
I'm kind of stuck.
I think the game has some sort of auto-stock feature.
Where if it detects you can't move with some input, it sort of nudges you a little bit.
Oh, hello.
Oh, I have no water.
That's actually kind of a problem.
What is all this?
No, thanks.
Oh, there we go.
Water for everybody.
Oh, yeah.
Fill it up.
Oh, that's gold.
I'm taking that.
300 gold already.
Not bad.
Water that thing.
Be on the lookout for hearts.
And you really need to look.
Sometimes they're like embedded in the rock and shit.
Like that!
What did I just fucking say?
Oh, can I get in?
Maybe from the other side.
Ooh, never mind.
Let's go from the top, I guess.
Hold on.
Also, call me crazy, but...
I feel like I've seen this before.
Like, it's definitely tiled in some way.
The map design, I mean.
Good thing that was coal on this side, otherwise I couldn't get in.
Oh, come on.
There we are.
Thank you!
That's sorely needed right now.
Holy shit.
Sometimes they're also in these piles.
Okay, maybe not.
Like this right here looks suspicious to me.
Oh.
Did you want something?
Whoa!
Ow, ow, ow.
Gotta take care of those shotgunners first.
I'm trying to practice looking at my character more, and it's making me miss.
I swear it's not an excuse.
I mean, it is, but, you know.
Shit!
Wow, he just shot me out of the sky there.
He was ready.
And it's the aircraft guy.
Oh, I'm gonna blow him for that.
That's what you get!
Revenge, baby.
Show me some more hearts.
And what about some wands?
I'd love to see more of those.
So this one actually produces light, because I have light on it.
I thought for a second, maybe it actually just produced light on its own.
But nope, it is the thingy.
Oh, no.
Ah, shit.
That's annoying.
Go!
We gotta wand!
Slime ball.
And you know what?
I'll take it.
We can maybe dig more efficiently with this.
No, never mind.
That sucks.
Oh, fungal caverns.
But look at the wands inside.
This could be a golden opportunity.
It's risky, but it's also very rewarding.
Huh?
Oh, god.
Unstable teleportation immediately.
This place is a mess.
Uh, can I get in there in a more easy way?
Probably from here.
Okay.
I kind of want to grab this and see what the tooltip says.
But let me clear the area first and make it safe.
Just in case I accidentally teleport into the unknown here.
What's that?
Critical on burning.
Oh.
Makes a projectile always do a critical hit on burning enemies.
That doesn't sound too bad.
If you put like a...
I was about to say firebolt on it, right?
Or something like that.
That's not bad at all.
That's pretty cool.
So is it gonna crit immediately or is it like on the second shot?
You know, after the burning has been applied.
That's like the question, I guess, that I have.
Bouncing burst.
Very low castile.
Four slots.
Actually not bad.
I will replace this one, I think.
Dude.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I will.
That is an okay want.
Then we have some...
I think it's acid in there.
Is that acid or is it...
That could also be level acceleration, maybe?
Okay, I'm gonna try this unstable.
I'm probably gonna die.
Wait, hold on.
We gotta take care of these enemies.
I need to read the tooltip on it.
I need to get to the bottom of this, finally.
Mix, mix, mix, mix.
Oh yeah, look at all that mess.
Imagine if I got teleported down there.
I would have a bad day.
That's a bad night.
Ow!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That hurt, that hurt, that hurt a lot.
Shit, shit, shit.
Let's not get into a corner.
Oh, Jesus!
Oh!
Yeah, this place is definitely above my pay grade right now.
Like, I'm struggling here.
Okay, I got him.
Okay, here we go.
Let's try it.
Fuck, I didn't get to read in time.
Shit.
And is that an ukuskibi down there?
Oh, that's bad if that's true.
Hold on, this is gonna go down there.
Uh-oh.
Please die.
There's definitely some electricity bullshit down there.
Is that?
Oh, no, it's...
What the fuck?
Oh, oh, oh, shit, oh, shit.
Oh, he's being polymorphed into all kinds of random shit.
Bad thing.
Bad idea, bad idea.
Let's not stay there.
Blow all that up.
I can't actually believe I'm doing this well in this place.
Given how dangerous it is.
Uh, can I...
Ah, man, the rock is gonna be an issue.
I can't get in there easily.
And I don't have anything else.
Oh, I forgot I have this.
I need to use my circle of stillness, man.
Damn it.
I gotta utilize it.
It's so good.
Put it on three.
Oh, monies.
And what is that?
We're in pheromone.
No, thanks.
I'm okay.
Uh-oh.
We've got a terminator.
Oh, shit.
Those guys are really scary.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No more.
I can't, I can't, I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
It's over.
Yeah.
I can't get out.
I'm so fucking dead here.
Yeah, yeah.
That's it, man.
It was a bad idea for me to go in here.
Uh, I got caught in a bad spot.
I got noited.
Actually, that's not true at all.
I got olivered.
Noisy had nothing to do with that.
That was me.
I freely admit it.
It was bad.
Why am I...
Hold on, my hands are very weird.
Okay, there we go.
We're back.
Unstable crystal.
I can dig with that slightly, so...
What the fuck is all this?
Why there's so much, so much of this toxic shit.
Oh, this is a great start.
Okay, so if I water this stuff up here first, it's gonna leak down and make everything else water.
Oh, no.
It's fucking cursed.
This is a nightmare.
Oh, it's toxic.
Why is it toxic?
Whoop.
Where'd you go?
Where the hell did he go?
Like, how is he gone?
Did he die?
I guess so.
This is toxic land.
Holy crap.
Very inhospitable to someone like me.
Yeah, that works.
Gonna blow that up now.
Make a big-ass hole.
Yeah, let's walk away.
So the unstable crystal...
I think that is really good against the fire, dudes.
Because they keep chasing me and I can set them as traps, right?
And when they walk into them, it lights out.
After a couple.
Not immediately, but...
Almost immediately.
Show me the hearts.
I want at least three hearts from the hemisphere.
What the hell was that?
Something big is going on down below.
Ooh!
Oh, no, he's gonna use all the charges.
We gotta kill him quick.
How are you not dead?
Did you notice my unstable crystal went brrrr?
Because he shot a black hole and it orbited the black hole.
That was fun.
So... my guy, are you dead?
I think he's... yeah, he's dead.
Where's the wand?
Also, that is... fire.
There's a fire trap in there.
Where's the wand?
Oh, it's here!
Oh my god, I'm blind.
I was looking only here, being like, what?
I can't see the sprite for that at all.
Okay, um, I'm gonna get through there.
Shit.
Boink.
There we go.
How many do I have?
I have zero left.
Shit.
He used all my damn holes.
Uh, yes, we can use that to get to the mountain.
And I will do it this time.
One of my words.
Uh, yes.
Oh, this is not... I'm gonna blow this up.
I'm too lazy.
Order me up.
Ah-ho!
Return... oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
All kinds of shit going on.
Wait, did they...
Dude, I think they dropped double gold as well.
They burned alive.
That also kind of counts as an accident.
Did you notice?
There was so much gold there.
I got him.
I think I need to start utilizing this accident thing.
Wow, they did absolutely nothing to this deal.
Sadness.
More water.
And then I'm actually gonna go up now.
Because I am... am I not close to the entrance?
I think I am.
It's like right over here somewhere.
We're getting that hard immediately.
Because that hard could mean the difference between life and death in the next stage.
That's how I need to think about this.
Like, it's 25 HP, right?
Having 25 HP and zero is a world of difference.
Okay, so this should be enough.
Oh, I could also go to...
The pyramid.
There's actually some...
Oh, dude, I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
We're going on top of the pyramid, too.
We're playing so try hard right now.
And you know why?
Because I am trying hard.
You gotta give it your all, right?
All or nothing.
Okay, I'm being very efficient with this.
This is good.
Yes!
If I could get that tablet as well, then we would be in an amazing spot.
Let's get the tablet.
I just need to loosen it up, and then it will drop down.
Oh, almost.
There we go, come on.
Come on.
What's stopping you?
There's a pixel of something somewhere.
Oh, that's annoying.
I can't see it.
Oh, fuck it.
I'm going.
Uh-oh.
Imagine dying to a piece of ice falling on your head.
I'm actually not sure that can happen.
I know rock falling on my head is bad, because I've had some experiences with that.
Including glass.
Remember that one?
God, that was...
What a tragedy that death was, because I had everything going for me in that run.
And then the fucking glass breaks, and everything falls down on my face.
Not a good time.
A very valuable lesson was learned there.
Okay.
So, according to the map, if this is at all correct, we should be right above the lava lake.
Skull is coming up.
Oh, but wait, what is this now?
Hold on, what the fuck is this?
Oh wait, I think I've seen this before.
Sometimes it's there, sometimes it's not.
Kind of random.
Here we go.
It's the desert.
Kind of a trek I'm going on here, just for that 25 HP.
So I clearly need to put something on this.
Right?
Like...
Something.
Something needs to go on here.
For sure.
I just don't know what it could be yet.
Maybe a tablet.
Nah.
What could go on there?
Okay, here we go.
This is the huge skull.
Kind of want to try and bring the pahasilma to here.
Because the pahasilma is an eye and that's an eye socket.
Maybe if we put the eye inside the eye socket, something will happen.
Makes sense to me.
I also want to...
Dude, I want to explore this pyramid more.
And there's a boss in here too.
In fact, there's so many bosses in this game and I...
I've only killed a couple of them, man.
They are hard.
Oh, look at these enemies in there.
Ah, there we go.
Yes.
Yoink.
And we got a tablet for our troubles as well.
A bit of a detour, admittedly.
But, you know, it could save our lives.
So, I think it's worth it.
At least for this run.
Oh, I could try and...
No, no, we're going.
I was about to risk it for the biscuit.
Maybe there's like a crazy wand in there.
That could carry us, you know?
Don't do it.
Don't get tempted.
Just go.
We go back to the hemisphere and we go back and be pet the hemises.
Oh man, for some reason my hands are like...
tired of pressing A, W, D and S already.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
Am I getting old, guys?
Is this actually happening?
Sometimes I do feel like a dad gamer, you know?
Like I've reached that point in my life where...
I used to make fun of dad gamers and now am I one of them?
Maybe I am.
I mean, the dad jokes have started.
That's the first step, right?
Let's try the tablet.
Boing!
Whoops.
I think if anything happens, it happens immediately.
That's been my experience so far with these interactions, you know?
Like broken wand, put it on the anvil.
Immediately something happens.
Or like put the tablet on top of the mountain thingy.
It's not like one of those Dark Souls type.
Sit here and wait for 30 seconds or whatever.
Oh man, this...
Okay, this was a detour.
I don't think I'm gonna do this again.
I am gonna grab the life on top of the mountain, but going all the way back here every time, I don't want to do that.
I gotta be honest.
I think it's technically the best thing you can do at the start of the game, but...
Nah.
I mean, if I find a teleport wand in the hemisphere, maybe it's worth it to do it just because you're so quick, you know?
Then it would be actually worth it.
Other than that, I don't think so.
Now, was this the...
Is this the game where we also found spells I could buy in the hemisphere?
Or was that the last one?
I think it was this one.
Oh, hold up a sec.
We got a shortcut down here.
Hello.
Wait, what's happening here?
Hold up a second.
What does?
No, it's just a little something.
I mean, it's going pretty well.
I found, I think...
Is it two or three hearts so far?
At least two hearts.
I just don't remember if I found an extra one in the hemisphere.
But this is a solid opening so far, right?
Like, it's very rarely going this well.
And I have a black hole.
Now you decided to come down.
Could I have died from that?
Fucking imagine if I died from that.
I would have been so sad, but also so amused at the same time.
Fucking tablet from the heaven above.
Okay.
At least all of this has been turned into water.
I have to use my...
I'm gonna use my tablet.
We're gonna make accidents happen.
Okay, that's a dead end.
People having fun downstairs.
A hamis.
I'm gonna...
Okay, fine.
I'll go around.
Oh, I forgot my tablet.
Okay, tablet this guy.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe these guys, it's safer to use my wand.
For the hamis, it's totally worth it, right?
Because they give the same amount of money, I guess.
Like use the tablet on enemies that are easy to kill anyway.
Or ones that are very hard to kill.
That's gonna be the rule.
I need to make a rule book at this point about all the rules I have.
There's a lot of rules.
Can I...
be a little cheeky here?
Ah, not bad.
Nice.
Does
it make a special sound when I crit?
It really sounded like the impact was different.
Man, I can't get up there.
That's so annoying.
Oh, we got a wand though.
Exciting.
Frogs.
You hear that?
I heard a...
Coooooom sound.
And I'm...
I think it's a wand.
Someone is using a wand somewhere with some kind of spell.
That makes that sound.
Barney!
I brought you some reading material.
Bro.
He does not want to read.
Don't throw that at me.
Okay, maybe I can finally get up here.
The place I've been wanting to go for millennia.
No, I can't.
Crap.
Oh, look at all these hemises though.
We're having a party.
Oh, it's time for the tablet!
This is the ultimate situation for it.
It's gonna be double the money.
Watch this.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Yes!
Oh, nice!
A digging bolt!
Yo, that's big.
That's actually big!
Amazing.
Water this.
Let's see how good it is.
Oh, it's totally good enough!
Is it though?
Hold on.
Yeah, it's okay.
It'll do the job.
Shit!
We have a worm.
We have HP!
Uh-oh, it's the big bad guy.
I gotta blow it.
Blade safe.
Oh, but hold on.
Where's the worm?
We gotta have a...
There's a very good chance that Stuart may be angry.
This guy's confused as hell.
Okay.
Tablet me.
Got it.
Let's go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
This is getting dangerous.
What is this?
Pheromone?
That's big!
We need that later.
That's pretty much guaranteed healing in the Heezy Base.
And also other places.
I wanna tablet him.
Wait, can I even...
I can't, okay.
Nice!
Egg.
You can stay there, Egg.
Is that gold?
I can't get in there.
Get the tablet in!
I'm getting pretty good at it.
I'm getting pretty good with the tablet, guys.
Money appeared out of the mountain!
The mountain is leaking.
What the hell just happened?
Cindy, the TV is leaking!
One of the best quotes ever.
There's the portal.
Oh, where's the worm?
Tell me it's dead.
Oh, no.
You bastard!
Shit.
Welp.
Guys, we're fucked.
I don't know how to deal with this now.
We need to keep exploring.
We need to find something that we can use against Stuart, because this may be the end.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
What am I...
I can dig.
Oh!
Please!
Please, no!
I can't go through portal, though.
We're gonna die immediately.
Okay, just go.
Fuck it.
Get the health.
Oh, no.
Okay, see if there's a good wand.
Quick.
That's okay, I guess.
Also, we paused game like this.
This is good.
I have no more money.
Oh, it's over.
I can't.
Okay, hold on.
He's angry anyways?
Go!
That's it, that's it, that's it.
Okay, okay.
Come on, out, out, out.
We're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving.
Just get the fuck away from this guy.
And we can dig as well.
Uh, that's a lot of mana charge speed, actually.
That's kind of nuts, no?
0.18, 0.6...
Yo, hello.
I'll take it.
Also, I need my thing on there, and this thing there.
And then this can be...
It's coming!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Stuart!
Can I, can I...
Okay, this is it.
He's stuck, he's stuck!
This is it.
I have plans.
We're gonna kill him through the wall!
That's right!
Stuart!
Look at this!
Yeah, you hate that!
You piece of shit.
Come here!
Look at you holding a stupid flower.
Hey!
I gotta lure him over here.
But we can totally do this, guys!
This is it!
Hey, fool!
I'm right here!
Come on!
Oh, that's right!
No, come on.
Huh?
Recharge!
Oh, this one sucks.
Come!
Okay, that works.
Oh, you're bleeding a lot, aren't you?
Man, he has a lot of HP.
There we go, baby!
Sit the fuck down!
Hand over that...
Oh, and dude!
The mountain has not even collapsed!
This is great!
Somehow, this worked out in my favor!
Also, I haven't even checked the perks!
More love?
I don't like these, guys.
They suck.
Vampirism!
I think that's an easy yes.
We're taking that.
That has been one of the most promising long run.
Suppliers.
Or sponsors.
In my time in this game.
So, what do I want to buy for the remaining money?
I can buy one more wand.
Or two.
I could get...
I think I like the heavy spread.
Let's get to something that also is kind of good at the same time, you know?
Like the wand itself.
It's kind of good.
Double spell would be cool to have as well.
Uh,
hold on.
Was this one that had some kind of crit on fiery enemies?
No, that was the last run.
I'm gonna get this one, I think.
No, hold on.
Point 17.
So, the question is, can we make something with this digging bolt?
That's actually the most important thing.
We need something that is fast.
Maybe that one.
Because look, it costs zero mana!
Zero mana.
It's kind of wild.
So, we need something with a very low recharge time.
Unfortunately, there's nothing like that here.
Yikes!
That actually reduces...
No, castalace, not recharge time.
But the heavy spread does something like that, right?
So, I'm gonna get this.
Uh, sure.
Give me that.
Also, give me all these, I guess.
Why not?
Throw it away.
Then also, give me that one.
Look, minus 0.25 recharge time.
So, if I can apply that to some dummy spell, then I'm golden.
I don't need all these fucking spark bolts.
That's it!
That is it!
Although, we can make it better.
0.7...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look at this.
This is it.
That is the one.
Actually, it's not.
Hold on.
Why is it not making sound?
It's weird.
Sometimes it makes sound.
Other times, it doesn't.
Look at that.
Sucks.
This is definitely the one, I think.
If I use another one...
Whoops.
I mean, that looks, I think, good.
It's kind of hard to tell.
I got to go test it.
Like, when there's no sound, it's, I don't know, you know?
Yeah, look, it's not, it's not super quick.
Actually, it sort of is.
It's not bad.
It's okay.
But, you can probably make it better.
So, this reduces recharge time and cast delay.
This is 0.5 recharge in total.
So, this is actually at zero.
Right?
If I'm not mistaken there?
That is at zero.
So, if I were to do the same thing here, then that would be...
Wait, why is that so much better?
Weird how this doesn't make any sound, but this one does.
That's my digging wand right here.
That is it.
We did it.
The digging has happened.
Very nice.
And the chain bolt is already good.
Like, I don't need more than that.
This is my damage.
I just need a better wand for it, I guess.
So, maybe that one or this one.
Something like that.
Yeah, that's, that's decent.
It's not bad.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Very cool.
Let me see this wand again.
0.15, 0.58.
It could actually be better.
No, it is not, it is not better.
All right, we have digging.
We have damage.
And what else do we want?
That's all we need right now.
Maybe I'll take this one instead.
Yes, seems good to me.
And now, we also have a holy mountain where we can chill.
The only thing is, I think the worm is still alive somewhere.
And that scares me a little bit.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Wait, what just...
Oh, right, that's why.
I was like, why do I have lower maximum health?
It makes sense, it makes sense.
Completely forgot about the vampirism.
But, everything makes sense.
Oh, look at the digging!
Oh my baby, we're gonna be making gold.
Look, even the gray rock stands no chance against the might of the dig.
The mighty dig it is.
The mightiest of digs.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's like, it's honestly one of the best I've had.
And just like that.
I think, insane.
Now, I'm kind of sad that I picked up all those hearts before I...
Before I picked up the vampirism, but of course you can't know that, so.
I have become the worm.
It feels amazing, yo.
All right, who wants some?
Wait, what happened?
Is that a worm?
I think the worm is here.
Look.
Yep.
Follow the tracks.
Oh, the worm has killed people.
Where did it go from here?
It went here.
Oh, I'm just, I'm following his tracks.
Where did you go?
He went here.
It's actually kind of exciting.
Give me that gold.
Whoop.
Someone's throwing shit.
He went up here.
He wanted to get to the chest.
Okay.
And that is a chilly egg.
The worm must have gone here.
Oh.
I mean, I guess it doesn't matter if he angers the gods, because they're already angry.
In fact, I have to remember that.
As soon as I get to the next holy mountain, I have to be prepared.
Because that guy's gonna be waiting.
So I need to be ultra prepared.
I also have to remember, I can drink blood, damn it.
Wait, I'm burning.
This digging is nuts.
This may be the best digging wand I've had with the digging...
Is it just called digging bolt?
It is.
The digging bolt, man.
So good.
Like, I've had them be fast before, but not this smooth, I don't think.
This is just perfect.
The best part is, I can sort of hide in the rock like this and go...
You know?
Gotcha.
Sup fools?
This is the ultimate safety.
Nice.
Guys, I'm having so much fun with this.
The digging is changing everything for me.
Oh, look at this now.
Rocks.
I'm buying it.
Remove bounce.
Uh, weakening curse explosives.
I'm buying it.
Burning trail.
I'm not buying it.
But I would like to buy it.
Not gonna though.
Like, I have infinite gold.
This level right here and this digging is an insane combo.
We need a victory swig for that one.
Didn't mean to do that.
That went a little too hard.
What the fuck?
There's another place to buy!
Thanks!
Um, yes, maybe.
Spitter bowl.
Do I want?
Yeah, maybe I'll do missile.
I'll do all of it.
Like,
I don't traverse on normal roads.
I go off-road, man.
That's how I rock and roll.
Notice how the sound is muffled when you shoot this through the rock.
Sometimes it's like, very muffled.
Whoa!
Let's get some more water.
Whoa, hello!
Didn't see you there.
I'm gonna be consuming his body parts.
Turn that into blood.
In fact, I need an empty potion.
I may have to...
You know what?
I'm gonna empty the pheromone.
Because now that we can heal with blood, it doesn't really matter too much.
Let me put it over here for later.
Just get it all out of there.
Nice.
Oh, I feel so good to have vampirism again.
Like, I'm not gonna say it's the best perk, but it's almost the best.
I think for me so far, the best perk of the game...
I think it's gotta be the change wands everywhere.
The freedom that gives me is unparalleled.
I think a close second is vampirism.
But that's just me at this point in the game, you know?
It's just...
Fuck yeah.
When I have vampirism, I'm like on top of the world, basically.
Nothing can stop me.
Except the game.
And it very often does stop me in my tracks.
Specifically a little stone with some fucking electrons moving in a specific manner.
That's all it takes.
What is that?
You there.
Don't shoot me.
I should make a feast out of this guy.
Shit, I drank mostly water there.
That was a mistake.
That's what I'm talking about.
I want to turn into a bat.
And fly around.
Soft blade orbit.
On... Poland?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
That seems like a bad idea, but...
I think it's good against Stewart.
So if we can throw that fucker on a trigger or something where we can get it away from us...
It would be nice.
I'm gonna take it.
Because we can't go up and change our wands.
Lava fell on my eye.
Man, where's the worm?
Huh?
Acid potion.
Yikes.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, wait a minute.
I need to take potions from him.
We gotta steal potions from this guy.
Question though.
Oh wait, did he die?
Fuck.
Because he drops potions that have 200% capacity.
Would love to get some of those.
Oh, oh, oh, come on.
I need to consider the fact that I can dig like this as an escape mechanism.
If shit gets bad, just dig.
Dig away from enemies.
It's genius.
Come on.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, we're getting so rich.
Oh, we have to remember, Stuart awaits us.
And my plan is, I'm basically gonna...
So, okay, I'm gonna pick up the black hole, of course, before I go to the next holy mountain.
Then I'm gonna make a hole through, just like I did here.
I'm gonna find a place where I can become a worm, basically.
And then I'm gonna kill him.
The same manner I killed the old guy.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
What?
Water, water, water.
Alright, also, can I?
No, I cannot dig brickwork with this.
I have to remember that.
I'm just confirming here because of the, uh, the incident with the luminous drill.
That was kind of a bummer that I didn't realize that.
Until so late.
What was this?
Why is there wood here?
Is there something in here?
Hmm.
Ooh, oh wait, I've already been there.
Okay, so here's the plan.
I'm gonna go to the, uh, fungal place.
I know, I know.
It's dangerous.
I understand.
But, the rewards are potentially huge.
Again?
A third one!
Explosion of poison!
That sounds interesting.
Missile.
Two-way fireball thrower?
Why not?
I mean, I'm rich AF.
Perch all the things.
Yo, hello, hello.
Okay, we gotta fill up our...
LUT bottle.
Cut up his corpse.
Oh, we're full HP.
Nice.
Noise.
What am I hearing?
I think I heard something, uh, burning.
Also, I need more water.
Give me that water.
Love to get a couple more hearts.
Just saying.
Oi!
Who surprised me?
Again!
Do you have a mom up here?
Kill him.
You.
Thank you.
I don't like that.
Can I not?
Wow!
Thousand gold?
I have never seen that!
Did you see the size of that thing?
Holy crap!
I have 3000 gold!
Jesus!
That is an insane amount of gold to get in a chest!
Get rid of that.
Now, I can't take through this either, right?
Uh, actually, I can...
I can get through dense rock, but not the extremely dense rock.
That's actually kind of good to know.
Good, good, good.
Oh, we have arrived.
Yeah, that's HP.
We can cut up his corpse.
Oh, we got to deal with the wand!
This is already scary.
Oh, shit.
Concentrated light.
The wand is not bad.
I may like it more than this.
No, hold on.
This is actually really...
No, it's shuffle.
I'll just replace this one, I guess.
Got another dude!
Oh, no.
Hide.
That place is insanely difficult.
I'm not going back in.
Not before I heal.
And find more hearts!
I need to employ my strategy of digging, actually.
Okay, I'm going to get some HP, then I'm going to go back in there, but I'm going to do my worm strategy.
I need more humanoid enemies to kill.
Not enough blood to go around.
There's a chest there.
More gold!
Oh, my goodness.
At this point, I would rather have health.
No more gold, please.
There we go.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Put that guy.
Blood!
Oh, look at all the blood.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm always so scared of accidentally stepping into this portal.
First, we drink off the floor.
Like that.
And then we...
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
You're going to have your minds blown when I show you the worm technique in the fungal caverns.
Also, I'm going to get high in the fungal caverns, boys.
We're getting high!
It's going to be a grand time.
Yeah, gimme.
Why am I still collecting gold?
I mean, okay.
Why wouldn't I collect gold, right?
If I see gold, I take it.
There's no reason not to.
Even though I have so much.
Come on.
Okay, maybe it's not worth it to go through that.
Difficult to dig through rock just to get that little amount of gold.
That's bad.
Oh, shit.
Didn't think that one through.
Okay, we've been here.
I really need to start looking at corpses here.
Is that a corpse?
Sort of.
There's corpses.
No, I guess not.
Oh, yeah, turn all that to water.
It's going to spread.
Got some blood.
Almost full HP.
Not bad.
I thought that was blood.
Show me more hearts.
Guys, 4,500 gold in the coal pits.
Isn't that nuts?
I've never had this much at this point in the game.
I don't think so, at least.
This is unheard of for me.
Dynamite.
Yo, this one is kind of dope.
0.02?
Only two slots, though.
Maybe not super dope, then.
3.61.
Nah.
Nope.
I kind of want to experiment with that a little bit.
Do I really want the saw?
I feel like I'm scared of the saw blade orbit, man.
I mean, I can get all of these, I guess.
I just need to go back and fix my wands.
Whoa.
A lot of magic missiles.
But I'm not intrigued.
Okay, I've been there.
Am I back at the entrance?
I am.
Okay, let's go in.
Not from that side, though.
We're going to go from below.
In fact, this is the only option we have.
Which one was this?
Ah, right.
Okay, we're back.
Let's see, now that we have all this money.
I'm going to buy this.
Take the double, put it up here.
I'll take the burning as well.
All these don't care about it.
Let's throw these away.
Then I want to get...
Uh, hold on.
There.
Take another double?
Why not?
Thank you.
Maybe just deposit these fire bolts here.
Maybe at some point I'll want them.
Don't think so, though.
0.08.
Why am I taking that one?
No, I want this.
Put this here.
The Poland.
Nah, not feeling the Poland.
Now I need to strategize.
Also, where's my black hole?
Oh, there it is.
Uh, put it here.
This is what I need.
So I guess my strategy is just going to be...
I go to the next holy mountain.
I black hole my way through.
Down.
I anger the god.
Follows me.
I do my best impression of a worm.
And then I fuck him with chain bolt.
A classic.
You can't go wrong with that.
Also, there's blood here.
I will consume.
This may actually be my blood.
There's a good chance.
Oh, it is so...
Nah, it's not worth it drinking that.
Takes forever.
Uh, concentrated light.
Oh, hold on.
Maybe we can make a better wand with this.
220.
Some missile.
Okay.
Maybe this one.
It's faster, but consumes mana quicker.
Oh, we also have reduced recharge time.
I forgot about that.
I kind of forgot we had all these.
Let's just experiment a bit, then.
I think I like this one.
And how would this one do?
Sort of the same.
I think I'm gonna put...
That's 12 mana drain, though.
So maybe if we put it on something with a bit more...
This one does have a fast mana charge.
No, I'm not gonna use it on that.
How does this look?
Even worse.
Okay.
About here.
That's kind of neat.
But also expensive.
Right?
Explosion of poison.
An alchemical explosion.
So this one I don't want to use right now, because I think I need to throw this bad boy on a trigger, just to be safe.
This one makes a projectile fire small fireballs perpendicular to its trajectory.
Nah.
It gives the projectile a shield that deflects other projectiles.
That is honestly not a bad idea.
Look at that.
The shield is even being replicated at each point in the chain here.
And it's not a big mana cost, you know?
It's actually okay.
Maybe I'm gonna rock with that.
Yeah.
And then...
The reduced recharge.
Can I?
Hold on.
I think I like the heavy spreads on there.
This one actually costs mana.
These do also, but way less.
This is a lot of damage.
This could be a big enemy killer, you know?
If we see something crazy, we use this.
Or a big collection of stuff.
I honestly kind of forgot how this looks.
I want to shoot it once, just to remember.
But I think we're good to go.
This is the setup right now.
I could even do this.
Holy shit, it does 100 damage and 117 explosive.
And with this one on it, even better.
Very nice.
Okay, let's see how it does.
Okay, it's just... it's that one.
Okay, cool.
We're ready to go.
It's gonna dig straight down.
Nothing can stop me.
Okay, maybe this brick wall can stop me.
Other than that, nothing can stop me.
Let's go, baby.
Oh, hold on.
No, no, no, no.
I wanted to go to fungal caverns.
Because I'm gonna pretend to be a worm.
And it's actually gonna work amazingly.
You'll see.
It's the ultimate safe way to approach the fungal cavern.
I think I may actually have found the way, you know?
Like, look at this.
He's scary, right?
It's very scary.
But is he really scary when you're a worm?
Just look at that.
What you gonna do about it?
Sir, where'd you go?
He bled teleportation.
Don't worm yourself down into the lava, though.
That's a big...
Wait, moss?
Why do we have moss here?
I thought that was worm blood for a second.
Here we go, here we go.
Shit.
That's it, boy!
The worm strikes again.
I call it WT.
The worm technique.
Also called the MM.
The Matilda method.
And if you know that, what that means, then you're a real one.
Whoa, whoa!
Oh no.
Shit!
Where did that come from?
Already I'm scared.
That's really bad.
Oh my god.
Toxic shit.
Oh!
All right.
That was okay.
We've got a mage.
Worm technique.
That's right!
You mad, bro?
Worm technique, worm technique.
Why don't we get blood out of this?
This is awesome.
Wait, what?
I'm confused.
I must have drunk something I shouldn't have.
Give me this blood.
That is concentrated mana, I believe.
Yes, it is.
I'm taking it.
Why wouldn't I take it?
Just drink some of it, too.
That's gonna blow, isn't it?
Come on, blow.
Do your thing.
Let's do it.
There it is.
Wait, we gotta do worm?
Stay in the trenches.
Stay protected.
Use the terrain to your advantage.
This is what we were told at the academy in 84.
Those were hard times.
Lost many good people.
What boy did we learn?
There it is.
I will get everything out of this place.
Oop, yeah, you know what?
I'm not gonna mess with the Ukuskibi.
We leave that there.
We are worming.
Kill everything.
You're not even dead.
Say what?
Got him.
The worm approach?
Amazing.
Ooh, hold on.
Destroy that.
Oh, don't go next to the Ukuskibi.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Stay worm, please.
Do not be a worm.
Only one rule here.
There it is.
Lovely.
Money, money, money.
I'm gonna destroy that.
I'm afraid of bodies of water.
Just because sudden electric...
Guys, that is amazing.
Holy shit.
It's Friday.
Oh, man.
That's lovely.
What should I replace?
Maybe this one for now.
I'm immediately putting this on my wand.
Holy damn.
Wait, are you alive?
Fucking die.
Don't even think about coming back to life.
Oh, this slime is painful.
So sluggish.
Much better.
I also can't believe we've only been to one holy mountain and this already feels really nice.
It's going pretty well.
Not jinxing it.
Yo.
That's where he entered.
Holy shit.
Well, I have a way back up.
Yo, that's actually...
That's really nice.
Not bad at all.
That is super useful.
I mean, I guess I have black holes, but still.
Okay.
It's time to make a sick wand.
Maybe I'll even do...
Oh, dude, it's spark ball time, is it not?
This is ideal for spark bolts.
Actually, we're going to test it.
I guess with the spark bolt, we can't do the worm technique.
It's like the big problem with that.
Also, it's really slow.
We need to put on something like this.
Still slow.
Wow.
That went crazy.
Hmm.
Maybe we don't want it that crazy.
I am tempted to throw things on here instead.
Hold on.
Nah, this digging wand is too good.
I gotta leave it like that.
Don't even touch it.
Just leave it.
How's this looking?
That's not bad either, but maybe this is the way.
Like, okay, this already does 25 damage.
So adding how much is it?
10 is not actually that big of a deal.
Right?
But it is better.
It is better.
But I could go for double spark.
You know?
So instead of that and remove this, we do something like the old double spark.
And we could even...
Nah, I'm gonna just keep it.
Don't get tempted.
It's a bit too slow still for me.
It's because of the recharge time.
What is it with these high recharge times?
That sucks.
Wait.
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Come on.
How many slots?
Two, two slots.
Oh, that's bad.
But...
No, it's bad.
And shuffle.
Dammit.
I'm just gonna go chain vault for now.
I'm not gonna overthink this.
We're keeping it simple.
Keep it simple.
Yeah, we don't even need this.
I mean, it does run out of mana quite quick.
You know what?
Hold on.
See, that's already amazing.
Let me see with the spark bolt.
Do I have one still?
No, there.
Still a bit slow.
No difference there.
And without this, it's gonna be super slow, right?
Actually, it's kind of the same.
Why is that the same?
This does reduce a lot of the recharge time.
Oh, this adds 0.75 castalay.
I...
Wow.
Okay, that's a lot.
Damn.
That explains it.
That totally explains that.
That's just not good enough.
This one removes a lot of castalay.
Interesting.
But now we're limited by recharge.
So if I do this...
Like, it's good, but, you know...
That's decent.
But I am just gonna roll with my original, the OG, and become a worm again.
The reduced recharge time.
Maybe we can...
So this is a bit too slow still, but if I do this...
Better, but it's still not quite good enough.
So I may have to use that wand again, but let's just see here.
Oh, that goes out of mana quick.
Why is that?
Oh, because of that one.
Still too slow.
But with two of these...
Actually incredible.
Also incredible.
The only question is...
I think this is better just because it's infinite mana like this, at least.
Now the question, should I be putting something else on it?
Does this do anything at all?
Yeah, it does.
It does actually work.
Okay, it's working a little bit.
And for this one, we're gonna put it here.
This is our new digging.
Should still be okay.
Maybe a little worse than the first.
It's hard to say.
And then we have a black hole wand that needs to be there.
Let me put all this shit up here.
Maybe we even do...
I don't even know.
No.
This wand is gonna stay here.
Because I'm gonna pick up the old one I had.
Yeah, that's it.
Digging, black hole, that one.
Perfect.
Let's go.
We have a bit more damage now and more mana on our main wand.
That's actually kind of important.
Let's see the digging.
Like, it's about the same.
Maybe it's a little worse.
But that's fine.
Can always switch it back later.
And I need to eat some corpses.
Do not move like that.
5,000 gold, baby, in the coal pits.
I kind of want to pick this up just to be safe.
I'm doing it.
Yeah, we can't have that lying around.
It's too scary.
I'm gonna safely dispose of this somewhere.
And that's my wand.
We're back.
We are back, baby.
Now, assume the worm.
Just don't drown in the process.
That would be lovely.
Okay, put
it here.
Okay, I'm definitely slower than before with my digging.
I can feel it.
Whoa.
That's a very low recharge time.
That, you know what?
I'm taking it.
That seems really good.
Destroy it.
Slow and easy.
We
got toxic rock over there.
Don't want to get anywhere near that.
Worm time.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
Oh, that was almost really bad.
When they freeze me like that, it's almost lights out.
Grab the blood.
That was very close.
We got to be careful here.
We got to find more...
Oh, there's blood down there.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oops, I'm taking damage.
There we go.
Heeled up a little bit.
Grab some more.
Nice.
We're getting a little high here in the process.
In fact, I'm not going to risk that right now.
I feel like we have a decent run going.
I don't want to potentially mess it up.
No getting high.
What's that?
Whiskey.
We could get drunk.
I mean, that would be cool.
With though, I'm not so sure.
The chain bolt is very effective against the toads or whatever they are.
That's Ambrosia.
He's immune.
Not anymore.
Oh, I see heart.
I see heart.
Nice.
We got to heal.
Also, I got to pick up some water.
Oh, can I even...
I could use a black hole here.
I don't know if I should do it.
I mean, I do have a spell refresh, I think.
What is this?
What the fuck is that blue thing I'm standing on?
What?
Oh, it's just one of those alters but covered in blue something.
That's all that is.
Okay, I'm actually going to get in there.
Fuck it.
Yeah, I knew that was going to make that into Polymorphine.
But I can get in now.
Oh, no.
Oh, this is bad.
I can't get in there without getting polymorphed.
Unless I'm very careful here with my approach.
What's that?
Oh, that's a decent wand.
0.05, 0.35.
Oh, wait, this is spells per cast too.
I don't like that.
Replace it.
Hell yeah.
You know, this is the situation where I feel like it's wise to just fuck off.
There's a wand right here.
Not bad.
I may take that instead now.
I keep changing my mind.
Thanks.
Now we make our escape.
No, we're going the other way.
Actually, I'm going to grab some blood here.
If I can allow it.
Yeah, I fucking knew it.
All right, wait it out.
I am so scared of being a sheep.
You don't even understand.
It's my worst nightmare.
Hello.
Why can't I destroy that?
Oh, I need my digging for that.
There we go.
Critical plus.
Just straight up.
Bro, I keep getting things I want.
I got to go back.
Yeah, I need to go back.
Deposit some spells and come back here again.
It's so tedious, but it is.
That's why I value the change wands everywhere perk so highly.
Just so you don't have to do this.
Okay, thank.
Oh no, he bleeds.
Yeah, okay, we're fine.
Just keep going right.
You know, a way to heal would be to...
Yeah, I know exactly what I'm going to do here.
Watch this.
I'm going to go fix my wands real quick, and then I'm going to go up there.
Bunch of corpses in the hemisphere.
Lots of blood to be had.
Okay, these are nice to have.
That one I'm not so sure about.
Neither am I sure about these.
This one is shit.
Let me throw this away.
And that one, and that one.
Maybe I'll keep one of these.
The light is nice.
I mean, I can just put that stuff here.
Why not?
And...
Just make a stack of these over here, I guess.
Maybe I'll use one more there.
There we go.
Now, let's see, can we do anything with this?
I kind of want to see what happens with this one.
This is infinite.
There's no use limit on it.
It's not shovel, right?
Okay.
Oh, okay, so that's all it does.
For some reason, I was expecting something to go...
Like a big-ass explosion.
But that is poison.
I guess it could be cool against certain enemies.
Maybe some enemies are really having trouble against poison.
Would be kind of cool to experiment with.
But what else other things could I put at the end of a spark bolt?
What would I like to have happen on impact?
Maybe even digging bolts.
Something simple like...
that, right?
That digs at the end now, but it's not that fast.
Oh, but that's gonna be an issue.
Unless we do...
Hold on, let me think.
Basically, I'm trying to make a wand that is for digging and damage.
Both at the same time.
No, no, this is bad.
This is what I want.
I need a triple...
No, I have...
This is too.
I can do something like that.
Let me see.
So...
No.
Wait a minute.
What am I trying to do?
I'm trying to...
Can I double dip on the recharge?
Possibly.
Whoa.
I can.
It's double dipping.
And it's digging too, right?
Oh, but it's not very effective digging.
It's actually kind of crap digging.
Wait a minute.
There's got to be a way to do something here.
I feel it.
I feel it in my bones.
Maybe with the two of these.
I mean, mana goes empty quick.
That's the bad part.
Oh, but mana charge speed on this one is actually...
Damage plus...
And the mana goes...
I go oom too quick?
That's the problem here.
And this one has 250 mana.
Yeah.
But the damage...
Yo, hold on a second.
Wait, why did I use a double in here?
I don't remember why I would do that.
That doesn't make any sense.
No, I had this one there before.
That's right.
Maybe I do something like...
That.
And then...
I don't know what to do, man.
I don't know.
So I need a digging wand, obviously.
Maybe this will become my digger again.
Just do that.
With that.
And that.
Like this right here is...
It's solid.
I got to leave that like it is.
Don't change it.
It works.
Now, the damage plus is so good.
I need to do something with it.
I want to put it on a spark bolt somehow.
And maybe...
Maybe spark bolt into chain bolt.
Or...
Yeah, actually.
Okay.
Still kind of slow.
What did I do before?
Oh, I had one of these, right?
Welp.
That could be...
Kind of cool.
Explosion of poison.
Honestly, I'm not seeing anything here.
I'm not.
And I also need my chain bolt to kill the dude.
Steward.
I got a...
I got a rock with this.
It's not super optimal, but...
Until I can find something better.
I'm just not seeing it.
Here, there.
What I really want is a...
Add mana right now.
That would be amazing.
Okay.
Now, black hole.
Put it on there.
And we can have some light on this, too.
Yep.
All right, let's go get some HP.
And now we go up here.
We utilize the worm highway.
Teleportation.
If I find another eye, I'm going to try and fill it with teleportation.
Because that's totally what I have to do.
It makes a lot of sense.
Okay, we got to find blood.
Blood, blood, blood, blood, blood, blood.
That's not enough.
I need a mountain of corpses.
The only thing that will satisfy me right now.
Man, this worm has been at work.
Holy shit.
Oh, look at all that blood, though!
Yes!
Thank you, worm.
Oh, that's an Ugozkivi over there.
That does not please me.
Full HP.
Lovely.
Kind of want to get just a bit more blood.
Oh, hello.
There we go.
Now we cut him up.
Two small pieces.
Oh, there we go.
What happened there?
That's not enough.
I need to be floating in blood.
We're swimming in it.
Oh, that's right!
I forgot about this!
Yo!
Sure, give me all that.
Holy shit.
Completely forgot about that.
Whoa.
Wait, is someone down there?
Oh, yeah.
Yo, that wand is not bad.
It's just shuffled.
That's the bad part here.
Oh, he has the wand now.
What a mess.
No, let's explore the rest of this place while we're here.
This is great.
Maybe we find some hearts.
Hello?
Such a weird experience being here, being able to dig through everything.
Whoa.
Cut up the corpses.
Get the blood.
Nice.
Full on blood.
Actually, there's a bunch of water there.
I don't like it.
Put that there.
Until we only have blood.
There.
Why is it such a struggle to find some blood?
Like, I need a big pool of it.
Oh, that doesn't look good.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's better.
Fill it up.
Nice.
Full HP, full blood potion.
It's looking good.
It is looking really good.
And, dude, we can dig.
We can get...
I know where there's another heart.
I know where to go.
We gotta go to the cave.
That 25 HP could save our lives.
He misses.
Oh.
Immediately got blasted.
Look at how much stuff I haven't explored up here.
I thought I saw it, dude.
I don't know where he went.
Berserkium!
Very nice.
Now it's time to get rid of the Ukuskibi.
Where should I...
You know what?
I'm gonna put it over here.
It's a good place for it.
It's not in contact with anything important.
It's at the cave.
I've been here.
I remember this.
The egg.
And I have light as well.
It's incredible.
Now I just need to...
Wish I had light on my digging right now.
Ah!
Look at that.
Got it!
I'm insane.
Unstoppable.
What do you say to that?
Now we leave.
Not here though.
That's destroyed.
Dude!
I know what's gonna happen!
So, listen to this.
Remember the eye we found in the snowy depths?
I think if we fill that with teleportation, a portal is gonna open.
Because this portal is gone now because this is empty!
This got fucked with!
So the portal is gone!
So I think we can open a portal there by putting teleportation inside of it.
Doesn't that make sense?
Like that totally makes sense.
Um...
Can I go this way?
Oh, we're so close!
What?
Come on.
All right, then show me the portal.
I know I can probably go through to the left, but I wanna...
Ah, there it is, there it is.
Okuskivy is scary.
And now it's time...
to leave.
Unless we explore a bit more of...
I mean, I've been so thorough so far.
There's no reason not to explore the rest of the fungal caverns to find more HP.
Right?
And we still have the worm technique.
Everything is actually pretty good.
It's looking good.
I think the bottom left part is the place we have not explored.
I've only really been in the top parts.
Like this place right here.
Unexplored territory.
We gotta stay wormy, though.
That's an ukuskivy.
Is that a mage?
Shit.
It is.
Oh god, I hate this wand right now.
It's so low mana.
It was one of those that teleport when you shoot him.
Or I teleport.
Actually, we swap places.
We teleport to each other's previous location.
The double teleport.
What's in here?
I want it!
Can I get it?
I can.
I'm gonna get rid of...
the tablet.
Yeah.
Tablet can stay here.
I've been there.
In fact, was that one of the ones I needed to bring home?
Let me see.
Yes, it was.
I wanted to use that crit.
Concentrate on mana.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
Take that.
We drink all of it.
And then we exchange it back.
Thanks.
Actually gave us a lot of full stomach here.
Satiated.
What?
How did this stuff up here explode suddenly?
Levitation.
Okay, that's the bottom.
Why am I so...
Why am I so slow?
Oh, I'm slimy.
That's why.
I couldn't...
I'm blind.
I thought I was maybe oversatiated, but I'm not.
Okay, clear.
This has been very good exploration so far.
Let's go in here now.
We remain a worm.
Murder everything.
This is how you do it safely.
The Matilda method.
Wait, I didn't see you there.
It's time to drain.
Whiskey.
I've been there.
Oh, here's that spot again.
The Book of Guidance.
Something about this room.
They hit something here in this room, but I like the ability to truly see what is here.
I'm thinking Wormblood.
Truly see what is here.
So, it's like an upside down pyramid.
Actually, is that the fucking demon eye?
Look at it.
Positima?
Dude, lack the ability to see it.
Aye!
Hold on.
I gotta write that down.
That's a great fucking idea.
That's a great idea.
Holy shit.
In fact, I'm also going to add this stuff about the teleportation.
Wait a minute.
Yes, yes.
Put it in thick.
Try.
Teleportation.
In eye.
In snowy depths.
And then, what did I just say?
Demon eye.
In fungal caverns?
Okay.
Now I will never... Also, what is to the right here?
Murder boss in ancient laboratory, demon eye platforms, explore that shit.
Get polymorphine and bring to stone west of lake?
I have no idea why I wrote that?
I have zero memory of why I wanted to do that.
Triangle thing in the art egg.
Oh, that one is done.
Scratch that one out.
Experiment with the music wand related to musical note in the magical temple.
That's a question mark, because I don't know that.
Figure out the music box riddle.
Yes.
Okay.
That's all good.
Back.
All right.
I feel like... I feel like I just fucking discovered that.
That was big.
I've only been here a million times.
At some point, the painting is going to drop on that, but...
Who knows, maybe nothing will happen.
But it does sure look like it's worm pheromone?
Ambrosia!
Oh, man.
You're putting me in a hard spot here, man.
Guess I'll drink the berserkium.
Ahh!
Do I throw away the broken wand?
Nah, throw away this.
Shit.
Get it.
What is that?
Oslavitation.
I'm going to get some more blood.
Nice.
A bit more.
There we go.
Man, did I actually explore this whole place now?
Oh, that's unreal.
Yo!
Oh!
Yo, not only is the radius bigger, but it's actually much more violent digging, too.
Like, it's super good.
Crap.
Actually kind of funny being this...
Yeah, don't get hit by that, please.
We don't want to be...
Why am I so slow as that creature?
That creature definitely moves faster in real life.
Scam!
That's a Kiva Skivi.
Blow it.
Water here.
Water there.
Water everywhere.
Like, look how slow I am now.
The berserkium was wild.
I should start berserkiuming everywhere.
I just don't have any slots right now because I'm running vampirism and I need my blood potion.
And I have a broken wand.
I guess I could throw away the broken wand.
And look at this, we arrive with full HP.
Don't even need that heart.
Oh, whoa, wait, wait.
He's here, he's here, he's here.
Uh, he immediately engaged the strategy.
Come at me, bro.
Drain the water, drain the water.
Sir, I gotta prepare myself even more.
Something like that is good.
Stuart!
Where you at, bro?
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
Actually, this works pretty well.
Shoot around corners.
Oh, but I'm low on mana.
Wait, okay, okay, okay, come here, come here.
Come on, come on, come on.
Just don't panic.
Play safe.
Don't panic now.
Oh, shit, he can actually get in here.
Oh, maybe not.
Get the mana.
There we go.
Stuart, you ain't shit.
Amazing.
And I saw this.
Look at that.
We've got healing.
But now that I have vampirism, it's sort of meh, I guess.
Hey, you there.
That's my home.
Can't get in here.
This one.
Giant explosion on slimy enemies.
That's kind of interesting, isn't it?
That sounds like a fungal caverns killer, doesn't it?
What's that?
Oh, extra perk.
Ooh, I may have to get it.
That's a good one, isn't it?
I'm taking it.
It's too good.
I'm kind of full up here.
Let's get rid of...
Kind of crazy that I haven't found a teleport.
I have short range homing and I have a rock.
I just need to find unlimited spells.
I say that every run, but I'm so close.
I'm so close.
Throw that there.
Okay, now...
What should I be doing here?
What's this one again?
Oh, Eldritch Portal.
I don't know about that one.
Double spell.
Definitely this one by it.
Personal gravity field.
I don't know.
Blood mist.
Ooh!
No, wait, it doesn't work with vampirism.
We figured that out.
Shit.
What is it good for though?
A cloud of blood mist.
What is the point of this?
Hold on, hold on.
What the fuck is the point?
Why would I make that?
Oh, this is Circle of Vigor.
I thought it was the healing bolt.
Oh, that's totally useful then.
Holy shit.
Um, I gotta be able to do something with the crit that I found as well.
Where is it?
I feel like I should just throw this on here.
This wand sucks though.
I really need a better wand.
This wand could be...
Ah, it's shuffle.
Fuck off.
God, I hate the shuffle so much.
But hold on.
Ooh, oh, that's good.
That's really good.
The speed up is all I need on the blowing lance.
Why can't I not see the damage?
Speed 350 times 2.5.
Yo, that's really good.
We remove the light.
And throw this on another wand, maybe.
That one.
It's the same amount of recharge on mana.
This is good.
It could even...
Yeah, I think that's really good.
Maybe this one is unnecessary as well.
I like it.
Do I get something else here?
I'll try that.
I have so much money anyway.
I don't really want that.
This wand could be cool.
No, that was not the gravity thing.
That was this one.
Get rid of...
That one.
You know, maybe this one is cool on a trigger.
Eldritch Portal.
So, the way I remember this, you summon it somewhere and basically arms come out and damage enemies.
Right?
So, maybe it's good at clearing rooms.
I don't know how much damage this actually does.
But it could be something worth investigating.
I don't want this.
I could...
Oh, that sucks.
We need a double for that, I guess.
Put the remaining over here.
And all my holy mountains are looking like shit.
I'm just littering everywhere.
Just put this here to make some room.
And then do something like that.
So, makes a projectile explode powerfully upon collision with creatures covered in slime.
Who's really covered in slime?
Trying to think where that would be super useful.
This could be nice.
No.
I changed my mind.
This one is kind of cool against...
Like, if it's a difficult enemy, you throw it on there and you run.
Remember, I did that in one of my very first runs.
Personal Gravity Field.
Temporary Gravity Wheel that draws projectiles in.
I mean, I'm happy with this for now.
Maybe I'll do that.
Experiment with that one for a bit.
See how much damage I do.
Yeah, let's try it.
And the remaining money.
What is that one?
Small explosions appear randomly over a large area.
Yeah, and these... I'm immune to those explosions.
I remember that one.
Give me that one.
And we're good.
Let's leave!
Time to explore the snowy depths.
And try out this new wand.
See how much damage I do with it.
Oh!
Wait, why did that die so fast?
What just happened there?
That was a bit odd.
Wait, what?
Is that rat attacking me?
Holy shit!
I think I just crit him.
So, I am definitely afraid of digging through water pockets.
Let's be extra careful about that stuff.
Ooh, someone has a wand.
Who is that?
Show yourself.
It's a sniper.
Okay.
That's how you do it.
We can still do the worm tactic.
Sort of.
Magic arrow.
Nope!
Ooh, sniper.
Oh wait, I can't even destroy that?
I hear shotgun.
Wait, this wand is pretty sick.
I'm really liking it.
Like, it's not fantastic damage, but it's like very predictable and it has a good...
It flies straight.
It's a straight shooter.
Didn't see that coming, did you?
Ooh!
Prickly Spore Podge.
I like this.
I like that.
I'm gonna go back with it.
And the way to find my way back is just follow the worm path here that I make.
Oh, that's electric.
Yeah, better get rid of that.
Where did I enter?
But don't go this way.
Man, I really need teleport.
You can go here.
Let's go up there.
Now a triple.
Yeah, leave it.
You know what?
I may just leave this here for now.
Up here.
And the reason is...
If I find another wand I want, I can exchange it.
Because I don't need the healing right now.
That's for later.
Let's not mess with that.
I'm gonna go grab my old wand.
And then I'm actually gonna try it, because I didn't try it yet on any of the enemies.
And it's the poison wand that I made.
Oh, I'm going the wrong way.
Follow the worm.
Wait.
Ah, there it is.
Give me that.
Is it poison now?
Or maybe that guy's immune to poison.
It seems very ethereal.
Oh.
Freezing vapor.
Wait, I don't need to wait for that.
I can dig.
Man, this thing really pushes them back.
Where are you?
There we go.
Oh!
Excuse me!
He died.
Thank the lord.
There's another one.
Can he kill himself with that?
I wonder.
Oh my god.
How dare you?
Where did he go?
Uco man!
Slime potion.
I know he didn't die.
You fucker.
Maybe he did die.
Shit.
Ah, whatever.
No, it's not whatever.
I'm going up there.
What else we got?
This is the way up to...
the hemisphere.
Actually, I know where there's a heart.
We could grab some health.
Recircum.
Hmm.
Yo!
We gotta test something right here.
Let me get rid of that real quick.
Wait, why did I move?
Oh, right.
The wand does things when you drop it.
Um, if I drink this, am I able to go like on a digging spree?
And...
Oh, I'm not.
Okay.
That would be sick, though.
Good thing we tried.
I will drink all of it, though.
And then take this back.
We do have black holes we could use to get to that heart.
But I'm gonna find more stuff here first.
Whoa!
It's wild!
Holy shit!
Precircum.
Insanity.
Oh man, stop!
I think he died from falling ice?
Did
I hear a sniper?
I gotta pick up some blood.
And destroy their corpses.
Sweet.
Vampirism, baby.
Oh!
How?
I was dodging.
Oh, that was
glorious.
Oh, look at all the blood!
Oh, shit!
My dream!
This is making me very happy.
Oh, yeah.
Drink up.
Stop that!
What?
I'm out of mana.
Fill me up.
Okay, we got portal here.
And...
I wanna find more wands.
Still have a whole slot.
Speaking of.
Fantastic timing.
Linear arc.
Why is that good?
Oh, it actually adds damage.
Can I dummy this?
Hold a second.
I'm gonna try and dummy it.
Yo, another wand.
Chaotic path.
Yo, can I dummy this?
Bro.
We're trying it all.
We're gonna dummy all the things.
Gotcha.
No!
I didn't getcha.
Now I got.
Now, what is the way back?
I guess just up.
Ah, hold on.
You there.
Ooh.
Look how much knockback there is.
Fuck.
I couldn't shoot because I had my cursor on these things up here.
When I was aiming.
Okay, so I know where I am.
Good.
Now I go here.
But I really need to find just.
Actually, that one is not bad.
I was about to say I need to find better ones, but that is decent too.
What about this one?
Oh, it's shuffle.
What is that?
Oh, bone dust.
In fact, that's steward.
The remains of the steward.
Okay, it's time to dummy.
Dummy testing.
Uh, get rid of this.
So basically what I'm thinking here.
I care about the stat.
I don't care.
I don't give a shit about what this does.
I'm only interested in the stat.
Similar here.
This increases projectile speed.
But it caused it to fly chaotically, right?
So if I can apply this to a dummy projectile in my chain that I don't care about.
Bob's your uncle.
Such as this, right?
So for example, if I were to do that.
I mean, not that I need to put this on this, right?
But the...
Oh, this is also shuffled.
Nevermind.
This puts down here instead.
And get rid of these.
Basically, the idea is that I can gain the effects of this on the projectile that I really care about.
And have the stuff I don't want, which is the chaotic path.
And the linear arc to be applied to the dummy projectile, okay?
So...
Hold on.
I also need to think about maybe I can do something better than glowing lance.
I mean, we have a nice big wand here now, actually.
We have a lot of slots.
Let's just have some fun here.
I need to just try things, basically.
So what do I want to try?
Hold on.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, wait.
These are modifiers.
Of course they are.
Hold on.
That kind of shoots down my plan.
Unless I can...
Unless...
Unless this goes inside the trigger.
Because...
Okay, let's see the main part of my damage.
It's not the spark bolt, but it is something like...
I don't know.
What do I have?
Maybe a second spark bolt.
What could that be?
Do I have a...
Or like a magic arrow.
Magic arrow.
So let's say...
Oh, dude.
Watch.
Put this up here for now.
Make some space.
So the plan is spark bolt.
When this collides with something, it shoots off something, right?
What's it gonna shoot off?
Three spells.
And those three spells...
Are going to be affected by these two.
Oh wait, that's not gonna...
This one is useless than in that case.
I care about the damage here, though.
So if I do like that...
Let's just try something simple.
This should add five damage to this, and it should not really affect...
Where this hits, right?
So I hit with that.
Wait, can that hit me?
18 damage.
So 10 plus...
Wait.
Huh?
Oh, this is three...
Oh, I'm gonna do this.
This doesn't do 10 damage.
It drains 10 mana.
Okay, it makes sense.
So three damage, plus five, plus ten.
Hey, that dumped me!
It actually works.
Okay, hold on.
Now, we apply this as well.
But we...
Do we apply it inside or outside?
Hold on.
Whoops.
40...
Wait, how did that do?
28.
Because that adds...
Oh wait, this damage affects everything?
So that would be 13...
Plus...
20...
Plus five.
25?
28.
What if I put it inside?
It's the same.
Right.
Okay.
Maybe I understand.
Maybe I don't.
It's kind of hard to say.
If we do this...
So one thing is...
Hold on, 28.
Let me try and understand.
Three damage...
Here.
So hold on.
20...
Oh, but wait a minute.
This is a triple spell.
Let me not confuse myself for a moment.
Let's do a double...
Actually, let's do no spell at all.
Let's just do simple.
Let's keep it as simple as possible first.
I increase damage by 10.
Increase damage by five.
That's 15.
Onto this, right?
So...
25.
Plus three.
28.
There it is.
Okay, that makes sense.
That makes sense.
Good.
But then sometimes it does more.
And I think it's because...
So the trigger, the way it works, is it casts another spell upon collision, right?
It casts the magic arrow.
And notice how this magical arrow flies off in cardinal directions.
You know, like 0 degrees, 45 degrees, 90 degrees, and so on.
That's the only way it can fly.
But if that happens to hit the statue as well, we get a little extra.
But that also...
So does that mean this is being...
This is hitting twice, then?
That's kind of crazy if that's the case.
53.
Okay, interesting.
Now I want some speed.
Better.
What if I put it inside?
Okay.
Doesn't do much, it seems.
What if I put this outside?
Like, okay, so...
Oh, actually.
So this increases the damage done by a projectile.
And that projectile is...
the spark bolt.
But it carries a trigger.
Which then...
What if I put this outside?
Oh.
Oh, but this is only gonna...
Wait.
Oh, yeah, it's only gonna shoot Cardinal.
Right.
We gotta have it in here.
Gotcha, gotcha.
Okay.
But...
We do have two of these, actually.
So maybe we do use a double here.
So...
We shoot this, and then it's gonna do all kinds of shit over here.
It's gonna do that, and then it's gonna...
What if I put this at the start?
Oh!
Oh, that's...
That's...
That's the one.
We just don't have enough mana.
That is the one.
We need add mana right now.
And then we're set.
Holy shit.
Hmm.
We could also give it some speed.
Do we want speed?
We do want crit, I think.
I guess put it in front.
Damn.
That's really cool.
I could even do...
Wait a second here now.
This costs way less mana.
And I don't care in which direction this thing flows after I hit.
Right?
I don't give a shit about that.
Actually, I do give a shit because I do a little less damage now.
Why do I do less damage?
Oh,
wait, I exchanged this one, of course.
I need this one as well.
Except, no.
Let's add another one.
Ah, hold on.
A bit over like that.
I just want the effect of this.
I'm limited by recharge.
Can I double dip on it?
Let's see.
What?
That would need...
Oh, but then this goes haywire.
We don't want that.
Unless...
Hold on.
Why is this not counted?
Let me think.
I shoot.
Why don't we put everything in here just to keep it simple?
That's weird.
So why is that shooting off so many?
Like it's going crazy.
And sometimes I only do three...
Oh, that makes sense because this is...
This is like the carrier.
The carrier itself.
Man, I have so much issue understanding this, man.
It's crazy.
Basically what I'm trying to do here, I'm trying to get rid of my reduced recharges.
Because they cost a lot of mana each, and they will contribute to a lot of mana drain.
And somehow utilize the heavy spreads.
You know, put these on a dummy projectile, like this one, that I don't really care about.
Well, I guess I do care about it, but...
I want the effects from this.
I want the recharge time reduce, you know, and all that.
Let me think.
So I'm limited by recharge right now.
0.25 point...
But I guess that makes sense.
Because I haven't gone all the way down.
Yeah.
What if I just use one?
Put it here.
Okay.
Better, I guess.
That's actually not bad.
That's dope.
I mean, I'm really trying harder to make something just...
That is somewhere close to some of the stuff I made in the past.
What about the digging?
What if we throw this bastard in here?
Reduces recharge time, right?
And it costs zero mana.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
What if we throw on another one of these?
Maybe this is the dummy.
Yeah, we have a new dummy.
This is the actual dummy.
We just need to make it a little faster now.
Let me see.
Okay, so recharge time is down, but we still have some cast delay on it.
Why is that?
This adds a little bit.
This removes some.
This removes, removes.
Adds a little bit.
In total, we should be about zero cast delay, no?
Why is that so slow?
Do I want to triple there?
Now it's faster.
Say what?
Bro, this is breaking my mind.
I cannot understand what's...
Okay, let's try and understand what the...
Let's get rid of all the unnecessary stuff.
We gotta do this one by one here.
This is getting ridiculous.
Okay, my plan is to make something that shoots fast, costs a little mana.
Spark bolt with trigger.
Check.
There.
It will shoot two spells, cause double spell.
One of those spells is going to be the digging bolt.
Okay.
Good.
The next spell is going to be...
Oh, there is nothing.
So it goes back to the front.
Right.
Let's see the board.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay, this makes sense so far.
Good.
And then...
So basically what I'm trying to do, I'm trying to make something that shoots fast and then put all the damage on the digging bolt essentially.
I call it a dummy bolt.
Or like a dummy spell, because I don't care that it's affected by heavy spread.
Cause it's not going to go anywhere.
It's just going to impact wherever it hits.
You know what I mean?
So if I throw on like...
This one.
I don't really care, right?
But it seems to not affect it somehow, which is super weird.
Like why is that?
Yeah.
Okay.
What the shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiit?
Okay, shoots two spells.
This is one of them.
Maybe we just need another one.
I mean, that's already...
Pretty good I guess.
Maybe we could just remove the double.
Remove that.
Keep it simple.
Then it's still kind of slow, right?
So that's when we throw on the...
This one.
See, that's not bad.
It's just super low damage.
Hmm... Hold on.
I need to test something really quickly here.
What if I just do... Let me see if this actually works on it.
Maybe I'm not understanding this.
So eight damage.
And... Wait, what?
So I do... Wait, why is it only showing sometimes?
Hold on.
Okay, so eight damage.
Now, it should be 12 damage, right?
Or 13 damage.
Yeah, okay.
Weird that it doesn't show me the damage every time.
Okay, but that's confirmed.
At least it works.
So if I now do this...
There.
So it works.
It works.
Right?
So I throw this on.
Okay, so now I confirm that it works at least.
It's just weird that the damage doesn't show up.
Like, you have to hit a very specific... I think I destroyed the statue so much.
Maybe that's why.
Like, it's kind of broken.
I guess I gotta test this in real combat.
Throw on the extra damage.
And if I put that on here...
Will that give me extra damage on both the spark bolt with trigger and everything inside of it?
Or will it only give me on the spark bolt impact?
That's the question now.
So let's test that real quick.
Let's get rid of these.
Now we do with only this.
This should do 3 plus 10, 13, right?
Yes.
And then we do this one.
So I'm hoping that it does...
31 damage, right?
18 plus 13.
Oh, it's close.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
26.
13 plus 8.
Hmm.
What if I do this now?
Oh, look at that.
Like, you have to hit the sweet spot, but look at that.
39 damage.
You want to put this inside of here, then?
For sure.
Actually, no, no.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Fuck, this is so weird.
Why doesn't the damage show up consistently?
This is fucking with my mind right now.
Put this here, put that there, put that there.
And that looks good.
Now we just need to make it a little faster.
Cool.
What if we do this?
Then it doesn't have an effect.
But double dipping, like that.
And then we double dip with this.
Let's see.
Is that faster?
I can't tell.
It's not.
The double dip is not real.
Unless it is.
No, no, no.
Why is that?
That wouldn't be double dipped.
Fucking hell.
I mean, I like it.
I like what it does right now.
Like, here's the thing.
It shows a little damage here, but it does more than that.
If I hit the sweet spot, look.
Oh, I run out of mana, right.
Where's the sweet spot?
91.
Did you see that?
And that was so cool.
Yeah, we're doing damage with this for sure.
The damage is real.
Now we just gotta add some fun.
We don't need fun.
We don't do fun here.
I just understand why that's so slow.
So we're obviously limited by cast delay right now.
Can we reduce it just a little bit for no mana?
Very little mana, please.
Oh, we also need this one.
Okay, you know what?
We're gonna be limited by mana.
That's just how it is.
It is what it is.
Let's go test it.
So we have that, and then we have digging.
Oh, but wait, we just used our heavy spreads.
Oh, but wait, we can dig with this now, I guess.
Or can we?
Is it gonna be too slow?
What?
Let me try an enemy.
Yo, look at the damage there.
Way more than it suggested before.
I am definitely doing something here.
Oh, look at that.
Look at that.
Maybe I crit him though.
I hate running out of mana.
Shit, stop hitting me.
God damn.
Yeah, I'm not a big fan of this wand.
Just because it runs out of mana.
It's a big deal.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Fucking hell.
Jesus Christ, stop.
Gimme blood, gimme blood.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
I can probably make a decent digging with the quick recharge though.
Let me go back and do that.
Hold on, actually, I have to quickly check this out.
Digging.
Nice.
That's exactly what I needed.
Fantastic.
Yay.
What are the chances?
So lucky.
So now I want to do this.
It's kind of slow.
Oh, not bad.
It's going to run out of mana, but if we do some quick digging, you know, that's all that really matters.
I'm happy with that.
I really am.
It makes me happy.
Now, the only question is, maybe the digging bolt is not the answer here.
It does cost zero mana.
That's actually kind of big.
Yeah, that's actually really big.
In fact, did that cost zero mana?
Holy shit.
So we have digging.
Put it there.
Now, maybe I'll get rid of some stuff.
We can put a light on this.
Is that only going to light?
Yeah, look, it only lights where it impacts.
Oh, and then it did that because I ran out of mana.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's cycle.
Like, it's not bad.
Some quick digging.
It's not as good as the other one, obviously, but it's fine.
It's totally fine.
Feels good to have a spark bolt wand again.
I do kind of enjoy the spark bolt.
This is infinite healing right here, man.
Like, look at all this blood I can produce.
There's so many corpses.
And I'll...
Oh, man.
Blood, blood, blood, blood, blood.
I should have brought my black hole, I just realized.
And in a pinch, I can also dig with this.
Because it actually has the digging bolt at the end.
I'm all... I'm looking for...
I'm looking for an eye.
Oh, I had this one too.
Is it better?
Oh,
nice!
Beautiful!
I really need that.
Soil plus snow pouch.
Whoa!
Dude, this wand is doing okay damage.
You know, speed on this would be pretty good.
I'm kind of feeling that I'm being limited sometimes by this low projectile speed.
Fill up my... blood butter.
I like this song that's playing right now.
I don't think I've heard this one.
No, I have heard it.
And of course it stops right when I'm talking about it.
Whoa!
I had a feeling!
Fire...
Circle of buoyancy.
I don't know if I like any of these.
Blood cloud!
I do like some of these!
That is insanity!
Get rid of that one.
Damn!
And maybe also...
Nah, that's it.
That's all I want.
Wait, he's blocking?
I don't like blocking.
Sweet.
I'm doing good damage against the mechanical enemies, but I guess he took some damage before.
Energy orb against snow.
The best snow digger.
Gunpowder.
I love the light we put on this, because it looks like a proper machine gun now.
Because where it impacts, it makes like a little...
You know how in movies, or also in real life I guess, when you shoot guns and there's this...
Sparks coming off where it hits, you know, if it hits some metal.
It's basically that.
You know, it feels like a proper machine gun that I have here.
Satisfying to shoot.
Look at all this blood I'm producing.
Oh, it's kind of annoying that it only lights up where it impacts now.
In this case here.
But it's okay.
Yeah, it looks cool though.
It's like a raven here.
Ooh, look at all those explosives.
Whoo!
Damn.
That's wild.
It's like a horror movie.
What was that sound?
Oh!
Oh no.
Oh, he's invisible.
He's dead.
Scary stuff.
Venomous curse.
What?
Makes the target hit by the projectile to waste away?
The fuck does that mean?
Say what?
What?
Hey, you want dance, buddy?
Didn't think so.
I gotta try that, man.
But on another spell, I don't want the prickly thingy.
Makes me...
That's floating in the air.
Isn't it?
Okay, there we go.
What am I about to say?
Is this Minecraft?
Acid?
Yeah.
Don't you do that.
You there, sir.
There's way too much blood here.
But I love it.
We're back in this place.
I think I can get inside.
I can dig, right?
Question marks.
Yes!
Good.
I mean, right.
For some reason, I thought there was a heart in here.
Book of celestial bodies.
Cool activity.
Hmm.
Kind of want to pick it up.
Mostly because I want to try putting it on things.
What happens if we put this on the anvil?
You know what I mean?
I gotta experiment.
We gotta leave this here.
It pains me, but...
The tests come first.
Hey.
Oh, we lack mana!
Can I get through there?
Yo, I can dig.
Oh, wait.
There's a heart in here.
Right here.
But there's no boss here, as far as I know.
Right?
Thank you.
Oh, hold on.
What's over here?
It's just gonna be the wall, right?
Just the wall.
Like, this totally looks like some kind of amphitheater.
You know, people sit down here and watch whatever's happening on stage.
Very... Roman-esque.
Ooh, hello there, I see you.
Damn!
He got fucked up.
People are moaning again in the...
magical temple.
Ooh!
Legit a horror movie when it lights up and there's just this monster floating.
Stop growing your blood, or whatever it is.
Bone dust.
Wait.
Did I check this wand?
Ah.
Alright, I'm leaving this place.
It is kind of interesting that there's this whole area here.
It's called magical temple, right?
And all it serves is to actually house that little cool oskivi.
Holy... what a weird arrangement of, I don't know, things.
Oh shit.
Do we have a guy?
A worm?
Thought I heard some electricity over here.
Dang it.
I am tempted to just go here.
But why should I?
I have healing.
I have blood.
I have pretty much everything I need.
I even have a shit ton of money.
I think I'm gonna be spending a lot of money in the next holy mountain.
I feel like rerolling a million times until I get something amazing.
And by amazing, I mean...
a ticket with wands everywhere.
And maybe... what else is really good?
What would be insane right now?
Ah...
Probably fire immunity or something.
Wait, what's that?
Hello!
Are you alright, sir?
He's dead.
And I have worm blood on me.
Alright.
Wait, did he die in the lava as well?
I wonder.
Nice.
Didn't even get to shoot a single guy off.
Come on, man.
Where the heart's at?
Hole on blood.
Anything up here?
I think we may have explored most of this place.
Let's go.
Fuck!
I forgot.
My black hole.
No, I didn't.
Phew.
Alright, let's see how good this is.
Sir?
Excuse me.
Oh, it riff...
Shit.
I may need to...
Revert!
What?
Oh no!
Asshole.
Wait.
Fuck!
I can't think.
Oh no.
This is a disaster.
I messed up my wands.
Fuck, he's coming now.
Oh shit, shit, shit, shit.
That's for you.
Oh no.
It's actually over, it's over.
Oh, I can't believe I'm ending it like this.
Fuck me, I can't get out.
Run, run, run, run, run.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Come on, come on.
Fuck it.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Uh...
Get rid of this shit.
Heal.
Uh...
No, fuck!
There.
Oh my god.
Okay, seems like he's not following me.
Oh shit.
Okay, what do we got?
Peace with the gods!
Do I want to make peace with the gods though at this point?
I feel like...
Hmm...
I feel like I can afford to be greedy.
He has wronged me in every way.
He has wronged...
Oh, he's coming.
He's coming, he's coming.
Um...
Let's see how well I do right now.
Okay, you know what?
Peace with gods.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
We're friends now.
Yes!
Follow me!
We're going on an adventure.
Come here.
Wait, why is my...
Oh, my blood is empty.
Guys, that was so fucking close.
I was panicking hard.
I gotta calm down.
That was fucking crazy.
Yes, he's killing things for me!
friendo!
Ah...
Dude, stewardess...
is awesome!
Also, before I go...
I gotta check out my spells, right?
Let's just see what we can do here.
We still have so much money, dude.
Ah... okay.
Is this music gonna play all the time now?
That's gonna be weird.
Oh, dude!
Luminous!
With timer, though.
Oh, that's bad!
It's the expensive one.
I hate that.
Earthquake shot.
I don't like any of these.
Maybe that one could be cool...
if you're doing explosive stuff.
I think we're okay.
Let's just move.
This is fine.
Come on, steward.
We have things to do.
Don't shoot me!
Oh, this place.
I'm gonna be bathing in blood.
Do not electrify.
Stewardess gone.
I need ad mana.
That's my one wish.
Evitational.
Follow me.
Also, is it like...
Did I get some kind of debuff in here where everything's dark?
I didn't pay attention to what the tech said when I entered.
Probably it was something like that.
It feels dark in here or something.
What happens if I shoot you?
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Are we friends still?
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to.
I mean, I did, but...
You know how it is, steward.
Man, I can't get through steel!
Fuck!
Oh no!
Scary, scary stuff.
At least we can heal here now.
What the fuck was that?
I would actually prefer if the steward did not follow me around.
Because if I accidentally hit him, he's gonna be aggro on me and I hate that.
I don't want to have that anxiety of accidentally hitting him.
That's annoying.
That was a friend!
Steward!
Fucking hell.
You're never gonna learn, are you?
No, I want to go to the right, because I want to go to the anvil.
Follow me, steward.
I mean, I guess he's gonna die at some point.
He's doing good damage.
He's drawing them away from me.
Get more blood.
I can't believe I'm still alive, by the way.
I was dead for sure when I entered this place.
Holy crap.
Steward take damage from freezing?
He does.
Come on.
Dude, I'm actually so relieved that we have made peace.
It's such a nice perk.
A bit more blood.
There we go.
Unstable polymorphine.
Yeah.
Nope.
Keep going right.
He's burning alive.
That's lovely.
Looks like steward is sort of stuck.
I'm sorry, did I hit you, steward?
Did I hit you a little bit?
All right, we're at the edge.
That means we're close.
Wait a minute.
Oh, that's right.
Huh, well, that kind of sucks.
Is this always here, by the way?
Yeah, it is.
There's stuff up there again.
So blood, I actually have blood.
There was actually something else I wanted to test.
I forgot what it was.
All right, let's get to the anvil.
Anvil.
Whoops.
Got it.
Fill up my blood flask.
Oh, man.
This game does produce some cool ass moments.
Wait, why am I taking damage?
Get more blood.
There it is.
Yep.
We made it.
Let's see.
Liquid detonation converts nearby non-magical liquids into explosive gunpowder.
Jesus.
Yo, look at the mana max on this wand.
What the fuck?
That's a lot.
I think I like the sound of this.
It sounds a little crazy.
Also, I want to try this now.
I mean, I want to pick it up, but I kind of need these other ones right now.
This one.
How many do I have left?
Two of them.
I don't need this right now.
I'm going to go grab it later.
I want this.
Liquid detonation.
That seems fun.
Seems like a good time, doesn't it?
A good old time.
Release the toxic.
And make it water.
All that's going to be water.
Uh-oh.
I see you.
Mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
Wait, is there a worm here?
Feels like a worm has been here.
Oh, wait.
Ugozkivi?
I'm afraid.
No, it's still there.
What is causing that?
Yes, it is.
It's an Ugozkivi.
Fuck me.
Yeah, I don't want to go anywhere near that.
No!
Wow, I saw that last minute.
Scary.
I like my wand, man.
It's not, like, amazing.
But it's totally decent.
I just need some extra mana on it, and then I'm golden, I think.
Maybe some extra speed, and wow, we're there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Stop.
Stop spawning enemies.
Wait, is this an infinite gold farm?
If you keep spawning them, I keep killing them.
It very well could be.
Is that?
No, I thought it was a propane tank.
Blow it.
Fuck, soil?
Oh, I guess it's their arboretum.
Come here.
That was a friendo, but I don't care.
I don't give a fuck.
Wait, why am I?
Oh, shit, I'm out of water.
I really should fix that.
Produce more blood.
Oh, that is unstable polymorphine.
No!
Okay, thank God.
Didn't have to walk all the way around.
That would have been a disaster.
Oh, we're at the entrance?
Funny.
Man, the freezing vapor is really effective at killing enemies.
If they just walk through it, it lights out.
I want...
Oh, that's the one I already...
Oh, this place is going to be a nightmare, because you can't tell where you've been, because it's all dark.
It's really annoying.
Oh, shit!
That was scary.
There we go.
There's going to be so much blood here.
Explode that one.
Grab some...
There we go.
Oh!
Is that it?
What's happening there?
Nice!
Dude, I am swimming in health.
Completely.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That did a lot of damage to me.
Gotta heal up.
Oh, shit!
I didn't see it!
What the fuck?
That was so hidden!
What?
Goddamn!
I did not see that at all.
This is why I gotta stay topped up, man.
That could have been a disaster.
Get some more HP as well.
Full health, nice.
Make a little nice hole for the blood so I can pick it up.
Oh, I see.
Oh, it's hidden there.
You see that?
Could have been real bad.
I can't tell if I've been here.
I mean, if I see destruction and shit, then I know I've been there.
If not, I have no clue.
And I guess if there's enemies, it's a good indicator too.
Bastard!
I tried to escape his shot.
This is insane!
This is absolutely just ideal for my vampirism.
Oh, I still need to find water.
And the good news about being bloody all the time is I get crit, right?
Man, this guy is really just hidden there.
Ah!
I can't hit him!
That is so annoying!
Oh,
he died finally.
Come on!
Man, where are all the wands?
Was his body on fire?
Dude!
Whoa!
Hello!
The energy orb is insane at carving up enemies!
That's my new go-to!
It's so good!
Fans, like, look at this!
Haha!
This blood coming down from above here is incredible.
The whole level is going to be filled with blood.
All the liquids together.
Come on.
And that's the edge!
Okay.
Also, I should grab some water.
Since I'm here.
Oh yeah, look at all these liquids.
I think I should just move on.
This level is kind of a disaster to try and figure out where I've been.
No, hold on!
Hold on.
We still have the part above the shop.
Oh, please die.
Oh shit!
There's so much blood!
God damn!
I'm kind of scared of going back to the hourglass thing, though.
Because of the scare I got last time.
Whoa!
I guess this means I haven't been here.
Because there's enemies.
Oops.
It's a portal.
With even more blood.
Is it just me, or has this run been extremely stingy?
With hearts.
Like, I have spent an absurd amount of time exploring every region I've been in.
And I've found so little.
Like, they just won't want to give them out.
Oh, I'm full on blood.
At least, note for the future, if I ever want to heal, just come back to a easy base.
There's pretty much infinite healing here.
Oh, hold on, that's electrified.
Right.
You know what, I'm gonna...
Oh, no, no, no.
Just leave it.
Play it safe.
Okay, so I've been here.
That's clear.
Yeah, I think it's time to leave.
Hold on.
Quick look up here.
Oh, I've been here.
Let's get out of here.
I forgot to...
I forgot my black hole.
Get rid of these.
And...
What do we got?
Okay.
All right.
Nothing extremely enticing.
Ooh.
Toxic immunity.
I wonder if that works against toxic rock.
It does say, and other toxic things.
Right?
I feel like I want to be greedy.
I have so much money.
Reroll.
Hey!
Fire immunity.
Yeah, definitely.
Definitely.
Okay.
All right.
Things are looking good.
Now I just need to find just a tiny bit better...
Also, I may get rid of the light.
Just because I want to...
have more speed on this.
Yeah.
It's going to be nice in the shooting through liquids as well.
Oh, I'm sorry, fishies.
Actually, I'm not sorry.
Fuck you.
It's a way to generate some blood, I guess.
I never thought about that.
But there it is.
Make some blood doing that.
Shit, how do I get out of here?
Oh, I don't...
Oh, how do I get out of here?
Fuck.
Also, I didn't actually check the stats of these wands.
Let me see the stats.
That's not bad.
Oh, but it only has two slots.
Fuck.
Is that any good?
I don't like any of these wands.
I don't...
Kind of sucks.
Oh, that one?
No.
Yeah, that's kind of bad.
Fuck, how do I get out of here?
Do I have any means of actually...
Oh, fuck.
I needed the black hole!
Ah, fuck me.
I guess I'm just going out.
Actually, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Maybe that one.
The nuke.
Fuck.
Is that going to be enough?
Let's try it.
I'm going to blow a hole over here.
Oh, hold on.
I need to be at a distance.
Okay, actually that worked.
Sort of.
Except that...
It's...
Wow, they're really angry, huh?
Oh, yeah, calm down.
I get it, you're angry.
Wow.
Jesus.
The only question I have now is...
Oh, I'd only destroy stuff above it.
Hold on, that's got... wait, did it actually?
Shit.
I'll try something else.
That does nothing.
Maybe that one.
Shit, I have nothing.
Giant explosion.
Sawblade, maybe, actually.
Oh, sawblades, actually.
Those do work.
Put them on.
Oh, hold on.
I'm scared.
Don't kill me now.
Please.
Okay, it works.
It works.
Yes.
Lovely.
Lovely that.
I just have this fear that one of these sawblades is going to hit me.
I'm going to get rid of all of it.
You guys are angry.
But you're not, though, because we have a peace agreement.
That should be enough.
There we go, fixed.
Fixed, baby.
What did I have on this?
I had...
Speed.
Right.
Diggity-digg.
Awesome.
Let's go.
Yay!
The underground jungle.
We have made it once again.
To the fucking milky infested area.
Fuck you, man.
The way we're just sitting there waiting is just not my cup of tea, you know?
Mostly because I don't really drink a lot of tea.
It's not my thing.
Yo!
No, no, no, no, no.
Nope.
What are you shooting at me?
Man, he has HP.
Way more...
Wait, what?
Your maximum health is temporarily halved.
Really?
Holy
shit.
Temporarily halved.
I'm considering some kind of exploit right now, guys.
I have an idea for a bug abuse.
Or like some kind of...
I have an idea.
Fuck off.
Dude, why do these small spiders have so much HP?
They have way more than their parents.
What's this?
Liquid vacuum field.
Sucks liquid materials nearby and releases them upon expiring.
Oh, I had this one before.
It was weird.
Ah, the wand would be good, though, but it shoots two spells at a time.
Come on.
God, I hate being slimed.
Come on, get rid of it.
Like, even having 1% slimy makes you so slow.
It's so annoying.
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
I ran out of fucking levitation power.
Okay, calm down, calm down.
Stay in a nice spot.
Take them one by one.
This is why I need more mana on my wand.
I'm too fucking slimy!
Oh, wait, this guy.
Should have some pheromones.
But I don't.
Fuck off.
You know what?
I am actually going to take that acid.
Because I want to try something.
Are you dead?
You're not dead.
Oh, look at all that money down there.
Get it!
What?
Oh, this guy has a wand.
Oh, glowing lances.
That's scary, actually.
Let's see what you got.
Oil trail.
That would be...
kind of cool.
Now that I'm immune to fire.
Wouldn't it?
That would be kind of cool.
I'm definitely taking that.
Holy shit, dude.
Also, get some blood here.
And drink it.
And fill it up again.
Nice.
That was a sweet pick up there.
Very nice.
That's the sort of shit I need.
I need more of that.
Specifically, Admana.
Ambrosia.
You know what?
This idea I have with Ashid.
I changed my mind.
I hate that idea now.
I want that.
Although, I never actually use Ambrosia very much.
Because I feel like it's...
inconvenient.
So I have to...
like...
make a pool of it and then...
sit on it.
That's just kind of...
weird.
Explosive projectile.
Which one was that again?
Let me get rid of that.
More destructive to the environment.
Oh!
Wouldn't that be super good in a digging wand?
Actually...
weakening curse explosives?
No.
Levitation...
burst of air.
Nope!
Stop!
Ew.
Now the question is...
Should I go to the Dragon Cave?
That is the big one.
I don't...
I don't know if I feel comfortable enough.
Like, my wand is good, but it's not like...
that good.
Like, it's not slapping, you know?
Like, some of my earlier ones.
Especially because I run out of mana on it.
Maybe I'll wait until I find them at mana.
And I'll...
take them on.
Are these guys gonna be...
cool if I just walk past them?
Oh.
Say what?
What's happening?
What is...
Why is that happening?
Dude, vampirism!
Vampirism is so good!
Fuck yeah!
It's the best things in sliced bread.
Oh.
Well, but I'm immune to fire!
What are you gonna do about that?
Wait.
Oh wait, hold on.
It can get scary.
They have my HP.
Anyway, so basically what I had in mind before...
So...
When my HP is halved, right?
I wonder if it is the...
current HP that I have that counts when I go back up...
like when the effect gets removed.
So if I just heal in between, like let's say I have half HP now...
and I mean like, I've taken damage half, right?
And they halved my HP.
I wonder what my half HP would be.
Is it half of my total?
Or half of my what I currently had when I got hit?
And then I thought...
Oh, if I can get hit while I'm half...
I can maybe just heal up with a spell or something.
And then when I get full again...
maybe it'll go higher than the intended number, I don't know.
That's why I said like, maybe there's an exploit there.
Unstable tilt...
Oh, okay, actually.
Yes, I need to see what it says.
This is a test for science.
You teleport uncontrollably every now and then.
Wait, that's the exact same description!
Is it not?
Teleportation unstable is the exact same description.
Oh, nice!
Finally!
I have been praying to the gods for...
Fucking how long is it now?
Four hours!
For more of these.
Finally, my prayers are answered.
Ouch!
Wait, I'm not immune to explosions.
Yeah, how does it feel getting hit by your own mind?
Dumbass.
Drink the blood.
Actually, I need to fill up my blood bottle.
Lay it safe, right?
Come on.
Wash all the blood when you need it.
Dude, I am so fucking rich.
Holy shit!
Get him.
Yoink!
Now we've got blood.
And I'm immune to fire!
It's ideal.
Drink that up.
Am I taking damage?
Oh, I'm poisoned!
I'm poisoned.
I hate that.
Oh, the spider legs!
Oh, that's creepy.
I hate it.
I hate it so much.
How are you alive?
There's so many!
Hey!
Like, okay, so the spiders are creepy and the design is insane.
Like, they really make them spider-like, right?
I gotta say, though, still, Rainworld still has the title for...
the absolute most fear-inducing spiders I've ever seen in a video game.
Or even any media.
I'm not kidding.
There's no movie that even came close to the way those things moved around in that game.
I have nightmares about that shit.
Oh, I thought that was like a 200% potion of ambrosia.
But it's not.
Fuck!
Get out of my way!
Let's get rid of that one as well.
Okay, one is down.
Oh, my...
The small spiders have more HP than the big ones.
Or at least it feels that way.
I want.
Actually, the stats are sick.
Huh?
It's basically...
Yeah, I like it.
Kinda wanna...
I'll come back for you.
Or will I?
Whoa!
Phew.
Scary stuff.
It's the worst one that just sort of appeared out of nowhere.
Holy crap!
I opened Pandora's box there, it seems.
Oh, and a spider!
And a worm!
Are they fighting each other?
That's awesome.
Please die!
This is what I hate about having low mana.
Or like, no ad mana.
More worms?
I gotta find a black hole.
Or do I?
Nope, I have sawblade.
Worst case scenario, we are fine.
Okay, that's the edge.
Nice!
Yay!
That is awesome!
Just make my way in here.
Man, I gotta take a piss real bad.
You know that feeling when you really wanna take a piss but you're so lazy you don't wanna go?
It's all so dumb when you say it out loud.
It's like, I don't wanna go all the way out there and it's like three steps.
I've been here, I think.
Get rid of that one.
Eh?
What a shitty wand!
Uh oh.
I'm low mana!
I need to make this thing fully automatic ASAP.
At least my wand does okay against the spiders.
Ooh, that was a big dumb of me.
I made a dumb move.
Okay, that's the edge.
I guess a spider dug there.
Ugh, slimy.
I gotta say, the energy orb may even be a better digger than the fucking spell called digging bolts.
Like, if I can spam this thing, it's over.
I can go anywhere, hold on.
What is this?
It's the exact same shape of a hole as well as the one we saw on the right.
Who's making these weird holes?
Come on!
Almost 10k.
Things are really popping off here.
I kinda wanna make a...
like a main damage wand using the energy orb.
I think it could be really fun.
Oh shit!
Spiders from all angles.
Okay, you're down.
That's something.
Another spider embedded in the fucking terrain.
And there he popped.
That's how spiders are born.
Plasma beam.
That's a very low cast delay.
Four spells per cast, and this is phasing arc.
Makes the projectile fly much slower, but teleports short distances over its flight.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about that one.
I'm gonna say no to that for now.
Okay, I've been here.
Out of mana!
Give me blood!
What is that?
Chaotic polymorphy.
Don't wanna get anywhere near that.
Gotcha!
There we go.
Full HP!
Is that it?
That's right.
Come on, be something good.
Critical plus.
Gravity.
Octagonal bolt bundle.
Makes the projectile launch eight magical bolts.
Huh.
I feel like there's so many spells in this game that at first glance you're like, I'm not sure.
But they could possibly be amazing in any given wand build, I guess.
I don't know.
If I had Tinker with Wands right now, I would totally Tinker with this.
But I don't.
What are you doing here?
Isn't that kind of weird for that guy to be here?
Or maybe not.
Wait, are we moving into...
Wait a sec.
This is like a fungal cavern, but for the underground jungle.
Why do I not have memories of this?
What the fuck?
Oh, it's being spawned from here?
I was like, where are you guys coming from?
It all makes sense now.
Fucking him is just peering out of nowhere.
We could get high.
I don't know if I should.
It's kind of a good run I've got going here.
I think it's a bad idea.
It is risky, right?
Like, it could fuck me.
If I do it.
But it could also be an amazing boon.
Why did not see that?
Oh my god, I've already been here.
Wait a sec.
Huh, dude, all these fungal places are meshing together in my mind.
Oh, look at all that blood.
Drink.
I haven't been over here, though.
That's new.
What's up, guys?
Oh, wait, I have a twitchy finger.
I have to remember, maybe it's a fire!
I keep forgetting that.
Maybe it's time to explore the Loki lair.
Am I brave enough?
I guess it depends how well I can kill the spiders in there.
I got a test.
Like, it's a crap shoot sometimes, whether or not I can kill them.
No.
Worms have been there.
Coming through.
The only thing I'm afraid...
Oh, nice!
The thing I'm really afraid of in the Loki lair are the clouds.
I believe that's in there.
So these spiders are actually okay.
It's the big ones that I really hate.
I mean, I hate all spiders, but...
How are you not dead?
We may have trouble finding blood in here.
Blow shit up.
No, maybe not.
I see some people.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Fill up my bottle.
Oh, my God!
They're all hogging the little toad man.
The Super Mario dude.
They're digging.
I saved this guy only to murder him.
Okay, come on, one.
Give me something great.
That's not great.
In fact, it's kind of poop.
Wait a minute, where is the Loki lair?
Is it up north?
Because I saw the wall there.
Hold on.
Oh yeah, my shit is fucked.
This is wrong.
This is definitely wrong.
I need to fix this.
I guess I can fix that now.
Let me see where exactly it starts.
And where that ends.
Play safe.
One at a time.
Look at how they're trying to get through.
So fucking creepy.
Hey.
Sir.
I just got weird.
I'm bumping geese.
Right now.
The geese are being bumped as we speak.
But it's the bad geese bumping that I'm talking about.
Oh, here it is.
So hold on.
Okay, so it starts up here.
Oh no, I don't like mysterious darkness.
That's horrible.
But we can fix map.
So obviously this is incorrect what I've got here.
Let me see.
How would I do that?
I guess I would just draw a line up.
Well, that's a bit too thick.
I guess something like that.
Approximately?
And that's how it connects?
Hmm.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
All right.
I enter.
But I will most likely promptly leave.
Oh, Jesus.
Can I hurt you?
I can.
Okay, that's something.
But I have almost no mana.
It's just the recharge is insanely low.
I need melee immunity.
This guy cannot die.
Fuck me.
Run!
My God.
I'm so slow.
I'm slimy.
Got him.
Okay.
It's possible.
It's definitely possible.
And you know what?
I feel brave.
Let's just go slow.
We're going to explore this place now.
I'm feeling it.
We can do this.
We've just got to kite them around like that.
And maybe we can explore up here first.
I'm not stalling, I swear.
It's just that there's stuff here too, right?
Stuff that needs to be explored.
That's all.
Definitely.
Oh, yeah.
I think I've been here.
Oh, hello.
Ouch.
How are you not dead?
Oh, that's the roof, huh?
That means there's nowhere else to go.
All right.
It's time.
We get in there.
And let's try and get this slime off of us.
Let's step in this.
Okay, so...
Oh, interesting.
Okay.
So, there's no entrance here either.
It has like a little small entrance.
Okay.
That's kind of cool.
And over that...
do something like this.
Like a tiny entrance there.
Good enough?
Yeah.
Something like that.
I like it.
Okay.
Let me explore the...
I'm going to do the outline thing.
See how big this place is.
We got to fill the map out here.
I can't...
Okay, I can dig.
Thank God.
But only through some of it.
Oh, it's fast!
I need mana, man.
I need concentrated mana.
That's actually what I need.
Sir?
Hello?
Oh, it's fast!
I can't even hit anything.
Please recharge.
Okay, I'm hitting him.
The kiting is real.
Come
here.
Okay, okay.
Where are you going?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want a loose spider that I don't know where it is.
That's the worst.
Even in real life.
Get him, get him, get him, get him, get him.
Oh my man, I'm trying to so slowly.
Finally!
Oh my goodness.
This is a struggle, guys.
There was a wand up here that I want to check.
Who knows?
Maybe there's an add mana on it.
That would be incredible, incredible right now.
Really good.
Look at that!
Booty trap!
Or booby trap, not booty trap.
That's something else.
Holy bombs!
Ha!
Not right now.
Oh,
this is not the entrance.
Here it is.
Alright, we're doing the outline now.
If there's too many spiders in here, I may have to retreat.
I mean, it is called the spider lair, I guess.
Can't dig through that.
Oh man, if a spider comes from behind right now, I'm actually fucked.
That's what's scaring me right now.
Oh, nice!
Reward it for my curiosity.
I have such a high curiosity right now, you don't even realize.
Whoops!
This bad.
Nice.
That wasn't too bad.
Could have been worse.
What do we got?
Nothing immediately.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Let's only take the shots we can hit.
There's two of them, fuck!
He's healing!
There were healing symbols.
Oh shit, he's coming fast.
What is that?
No, we're going, we're going, we're going!
Fuck this place.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
If one of you come, I can take you on.
No, no, no, no, don't, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No more than one.
Don't get slimed, damn it.
I kind of don't want to lead them back to my home base here.
I gotta kill them.
Oh shit!
Oh no!
Guys, I may be, I may be dead.
I'm wandering into unexplored territory here.
Phew, get away from these guys.
Maybe they lost aggro on me.
And now I go in their cave.
Fuck all y'all.
It's my turn.
That's right, they lost track of me I think.
That's how you do it, you lead them out and then you go in.
Seems legit.
Now please reward me.
Show me the goods.
I mean there's fungus.
That could maybe be nice.
Wait, where did I go before?
Because my game is lagging again.
Okay, okay, okay.
This is where I was, I think.
Dead end.
Oh, I see a spider.
Did I come, did I go through there?
I think I did.
Yeah, that looks like the diggings of me.
No!
It's over.
Shit.
I can't, I have no teleport.
Leave.
Never to come back, never to come back, never to come back.
Get the fuck out of that place.
Yup.
We're gonna go out there and heal now.
And then we're gonna go to home base.
Oh, look at all that blood, that's lovely.
That's exactly what a man needs.
I mean a vampire.
I'm not a mere mortal.
Grab some more.
Eat it off the floor.
Now where are the spiders, that's what I want to know.
Where are the big dudes at?
They're just roaming out here somewhere.
That's a scary thought.
Did I check this?
I did.
In fact, I kind of just want to go back and make a wand out of this.
Because I'm immune to fire, I can probably make something cool.
But hold on.
Gotta find some blood first.
Ouch.
Whee, that's lava.
And that's a worm!
Oh, shit, that could have been real bad.
Wow.
When you're stuck in the worm tunnel and they're after you, it's really bad.
Okay, we're losing a lot of HP here.
Oh, hello.
Sitting there waiting.
Doesn't that look like a face of a fish?
That's the mouth, that's the eye, and those are the tails.
That's a fish right there.
That's one of those fish crackers you can eat.
That people really enjoy.
Whoa!
Now we're back in the mushroomy cave.
Alright, now we go up.
Exactly.
I had a feeling I didn't have a feeling.
I got lucky AF.
You know what, that's what I need right now.
I need to be lucky AF.
I need all the luck I can get.
Skill is just not enough, obviously.
I need that luck on my side.
Eh.
Let's go back up here.
Why are you in my house?
Fuck off.
Not allowed.
Something I've noticed, when the enemies walk through this area up here, the gods are not angry.
Or like the, I mean, the holy temple doesn't collapse.
It's only when I do it.
Okay, so let's see here.
I have this one.
I thought it would be cool to make something with it and that.
You know, just set everything on fire!
The fuck, man?
The hell?
No.
Okay.
Also...
Actually, this is a pretty good wand.
In itself, I never even looked at the stats.
.17?
Dude, that's even...
Dude, this is better than my current wand!
This is just straight up upgrade.
No fucking way!
Yo, that's easy.
Let's see.
Oh!
My god!
Oh my god!
That's amazing!
And look, I can shoot it for so much longer too!
Oh my goodness, that's so good!
Can we make it even better now?
What if I do this?
Is that nuts?
Oh wow, that makes me oom quick, right, because this costs zero mana, right.
Bad idea, bad idea.
I still kind of want an add mana though.
But this is a significant upgrade, holy shit!
I could even... no, that's too much mana.
Way too much mana.
Dude, that's awesome!
I was expecting to get ready to sit here and figure something out for like ten hours.
But that's nice.
Also, this one, liquid detonation, is intriguing to me.
Maybe I'll put light back on here as well.
I do like the light, but I like it even more when the light is on my initial.
That way we have light all the way.
I enjoy that one!
Formation above and below...
Nope.
Eh?
Wait a minute, is this gonna affect...
Hold on, let me get rid of this.
No way!
Okay, nevermind, nevermind.
I thought maybe it did something, but it didn't.
It did not do the thing, I thought it would do diddly do dong.
Ding dong.
Okay, so now we can maybe make a better digging one with some of the other ones we have.
Like that one!
But look at the mana recharge, that's disgusting.
That makes me want to puke.
What about this one though?
Ooh, homing!
Nice.
Oh, that's slow as hell!
I think I hate that.
Wait, do we even read this right now?
I need this.
We do need that.
What else do we have?
I'm looking at the stats of all these right now.
Eh.
Eh, I think this is the one.
If we don't do that...
This may even be better for the digging.
Nope, no, it's not.
I like that more.
Okay, now with the fire arc.
If we do something like...
Fire arc on...
If we then do it...
Okay, watch this.
There.
You see the fire arc?
I don't want to shoot it to the sides though, I want to make like a bifurcation here.
I think I may have thrown away all my bifurcations because I almost never used them.
Dang it.
Where did I leave it?
Did I leave it in the other holy mountain?
Fuck me.
Unless there's one of these.
There's that one, I guess.
Quadruple.
Wait, what?
No, yeah, yeah.
Take that, I guess.
Water trail.
Maybe I'll take one of these as two.
That's 35 mana drain.
Yeah, that's shit, don't want that.
I don't think I like the chaotic path.
And you know what, I do like the chaotic path.
I don't like this one.
Throw that away.
We also have this one, we have to remember that.
We have the healing on it.
Let me quickly grab this so we can take this one.
And put it somewhere.
That I don't care about.
I don't care about that either.
How's this want?
0.22.
Actually not the worst.
Yeah.
Let me keep this spell up here.
This one is empty anyway, fuck it.
Cares about nuke.
I don't like that either.
This one, I'm very curious about that one.
Let's try it.
Put something on, let's put it on magic.
Hold on, so this is a projectile modifier.
Projectile modifier.
Yeah, just put it on that, I guess.
That's fine.
To waste away.
Huh.
That's interesting.
Okay, let's go.
Now I kind of feel like I have rejuvenated strength to go back to...
No, I don't want to go to Loki lair because of the fucking clouds.
I don't have a teleport bolt.
That's a nightmare without that.
Oh my god, this one is so much better now.
It also shoots faster, I think.
Oh yeah, definitely faster.
This is a wild upgrade.
Right, there's also this one.
But...
I'm not feeling it.
Not feeling that one.
I do feel this blood though.
It goes in my tummy.
Where it belongs.
More blood.
Grab it.
And some over here.
Eh, that wasn't too much.
I'm going.
Am I?
I got that, I got that.
I'm going.
The gods...
Yeah, you better fucking look the other way.
Assholes.
That's a lot of mana on that wand.
That's a lot of mana charge.
Ooh, this one is not bad either.
That's a pretty good wand.
What is that?
Is that...
Is that my laser cutter?
Holy shit, finally.
Personal plasma beam.
I don't like that.
Reach, re-roll.
Permanent shield is an option.
Trick read.
4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident.
Cool.
But I don't want that.
I have way too much money.
Like, this is cool.
I'm tempted to re-roll just because I have so much money.
Ooh, I'm taking it though.
It's good, man.
Like, the shield is actually fantastic.
Now give me this.
Look at that.
My beloved.
Oh, that's so lovely.
Hold on.
It's scary.
If I accidentally walk into this one...
Ooh, that's bad.
That's real bad.
And hold on, where am I now?
I am in...
Wait a minute.
Where the fuck am I?
It's vault time.
I don't think there's going to be a lot of stuff that I can dig through with the energy orb here anyway.
It has to be the laser cutter now.
We're cutting with laser, baby.
Yeah.
Fuck the energy orb for now.
All of these can sort of...
Fuck off.
I guess.
I don't need that many.
Maybe I'll take one more to have in my bar up here.
How about two plasma cutters?
And then...
This wand is nice.
That's a nice wand.
Maybe it's even better for this.
I gotta see it.
I can't look at stats.
Okay, so it's a little slow.
Can we make that better?
Dude.
No, this is the low mana charge.
Ah, wait a minute.
Actually.
We removed that even.
Dude, that's actually not bad.
Ooh, we can...
Damn!
I want to see that in action.
That's effective.
Look how bright it is.
That's cool.
Maybe a bit too much.
Maybe you can go a little too nuts with this.
It's very dangerous.
The thing I don't like about it, though, is...
Look at the mana charge speed.
Like, if you use this a couple times, and let's say you need to make an escape...
You can't do it.
Though I may just put it back down here.
It was a cool idea, though.
In fact, I don't know what to put on this one.
Usually I have a teleport by now or something.
I don't know what to do with my wands.
Well, I guess we make that.
Yeah, that's good.
That's actually... that's solid.
Leave it like that.
I don't want to mess with it anymore.
We're done with that.
And then on one of the other wands here...
Maybe I'll just have some...
healing.
Maybe some healing.
Keep it simple.
Maybe a waste.
0.32.
Actually, if I only have one here...
Oh yeah, the mana's never gonna...
That's actually totally fine.
I'm gonna leave it like that, I think.
That's my digging wand.
I can still have an energy orb, I guess.
I can have both.
Why not both?
Why not two digging wands?
And then we'll leave this here so we can pick up a replacement for this one.
I also don't like that it always casts this whatever thing.
So, whatever.
Yeah.
We're doing that.
Alright, let's go!
We're moving on.
The vault!
Also, I gotta take a piss.
I can't... I gotta go now.
Be right back.
Boink!
I'm back!
What's up, boys?
Oh, the wand is amazing now.
I think these guys have more HP in the vault than they do elsewhere.
The sound of this wand is satisfying.
It's just a brrrp.
Like, I've had fast wands before, but I do love the sound of the sparkwalls shooting fast.
It makes me happy.
I thought you died.
Ooh, that's lava!
Oh, that's not... that's green!
What am I doing here, man?
I'm terrible.
Okay, so now it's time for the...
Plasma Cutter.
Oh yeah, this is actually way more convenient.
No!
That was a close one.
By the way, am I doing less damage right now with my wand?
I feel like it just kind of sucks now.
Like, did I accidentally fuck it up?
Moving some things around?
You know what, I have to remember that my normal digging wand is on this one.
I gotta put my special digging wand on four.
So I can do stuff like that.
Because it is more safe to dig with the energy orb.
Plasma Cutter does have some dangers associated with it.
Dude, the crazy thing is...
This wand up here instantly recharges.
Look at this.
Watch now.
Insta.
I don't need Admana.
This is...
wild.
It's way better than I thought.
My keyboard is...
There was some kind of thing on my keyboard.
I had to get it off.
There we go.
The thing about this wand though, it sucks against these small enemies.
Oh no.
Oh, it's getting out of control.
Okay, don't panic.
Don't panic.
Go to a safe spot.
And stay.
Safe spot and stay there.
Okay, we're safe here.
Panic management.
Just stay here.
Let them come in one by one.
Just wait for a bit.
I'm proud of myself.
I could have easily just lost everything there.
Because I usually panic in those situations and just...
I don't even know.
Let's find some blood.
We got some here.
Oh.
Did I just release some acid by killing these guys?
Oh wait, I'm fire immune.
Keep forgetting.
Yikes.
Who's shooting that?
Oh no.
Oh, I've got to switch your fingers.
Who is shooting that shit?
That is so annoying.
How is these guys?
I mean, as long as they pour in one by one like that, I'm totally okay with it.
Shit.
I need to.
There we go.
I think I just picked up some toxic shit.
Yep.
Or some poison.
I wonder if there's a perk to get like infinite levitation.
You can just hold the button forever.
It'd be fun, I guess.
What is that?
It's a big bomb.
All right, it's going pretty well.
I just need to heal.
We're bound to find a spot with a lot of organic enemies and we're going to make a big pile of blood and we're just going to gorge ourselves.
It's going to be great.
That's just not enough blood for me.
I need more.
I'm a needy vampire.
Shit!
I'm fine.
Getting a little low, though.
What's that?
Visebleum.
You know what?
I'm tired of carrying around the Kulu Skibi.
I think it's called music stone.
I think Skibi means stone.
Oh!
You bastard!
Look at all that fire.
I'm tempted to just go through because there's no reason not to.
Yeah, we're going.
I can always go back.
I have the laser cutter, baby.
Maybe I should just heal.
I think it's the safer thing to do.
May as well do it.
Yeah, why not?
Let's see what we got.
Ooh!
Okay.
Nope.
What's that?
More additional spell slots.
Nope.
I'm going to be super greedy here, guys.
Now that!
I think I may leave this here and come back and grab that.
When I've gathered more hearts.
Because let's say I get to like...
I'm also going to go back to the earlier regions and explore them fully.
You know, get all the hearts.
We grab this.
Ooh, that's big.
That's big.
Hmm.
What's this one?
Protectile slower.
Revenge bullets.
I mean, that's actually not bad either.
Right?
That's just like 20% damage reduction.
Against most shit that you're going to encounter.
Pretty dope.
Let me see the wands.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I had an idea.
No, no, no, no, no.
Nevermind, nevermind.
Okay, I'm not, I don't like these wands.
But like, where's my teleport?
For fuck's sake.
Like, what are we doing here?
I've... what?
Not a single teleport.
That's just incredible, actually.
Wait a minute, where's my...
Oh, there's my healing.
Uh...
Yeah.
I'm just going to dig right back up.
As crazy as it sounds.
There we go.
Oh, let's make it a little bit wider.
Look the other way.
Yep.
Yeah, don't stand too close.
Dude, I swear to God, my heart rate jumped a million percent.
I wish there was a perk.
Your spells can no longer hurt you.
Why is everything burning?
Oh, hello.
I was born in fire.
And we're right back in it, huh?
Enemies from all sides.
Okay.
Wait, what happened there?
Oh, I guess a bunch of acid.
Blow it up.
What the f...
Why are these guys stuck in the wall?
Oh, you know what it is?
Oh, actually, I don't know if that's possible.
So I was thinking maybe they hit some, uh, teleportation.
And they got teleported into a wall.
I don't think that's the thing.
Because I feel like that would have happened to me by now.
At some point.
Given my luck.
That would have been a thing.
For sure.
Wait, why is the blood disappearing when I...
Huh?
Why isn't there a massive amount of blood coming out when I chop up their corpses?
Come on!
There we go.
I was about to say, I don't even need the money, but I actually do.
I really do.
I need the money for re-rolls.
In fact, we only have...
Let me think.
Uh...
One left.
One perk left to choose, I think.
Whoops.
I'm doing pretty well not taking too much damage.
But I'm not finding a lot of blood.
Yeah, what's that?
Oh, this is where I was before.
I'll go around.
Heh.
Piece of machinery fell.
What a mess!
Much annoying enemies.
But there's blood everywhere.
Except...
There's so little I don't understand.
Like, I'm chopping up their...
Did I do something to my wand here where...
The chopping up is not actually working as they expected anymore?
Very weird.
My chop is no longer, uh...
Good chop.
Oh no.
Did you try to teleport me, sir?
God, it's actually fucking impossible to kill these guys.
What's this?
Recircu- Water and levitation.
Okay, we're safe.
And honey.
I guess I know how Hamises are made now.
They're made in tiny nests like that.
What's happening here?
Oh, it's the edge.
Okay.
But is there anything?
Like, look at that.
There's like a little hole there.
Hold on.
Do not hit yourself now, please.
I don't trust it.
Go like this.
What is this?
A gold bar!
Huh!
Cool?
Is that always here?
Okay, dude.
I'm gonna dig.
And you may ask...
Gosh, Oliver, where are you digging?
And my answer is...
to the right.
And that's the end of that answer.
I have no idea where I'm ending up.
But I am going.
Am I gonna encounter some insanely dense rock at some point?
I wish I had the all-seeing eye right now.
Don't walk into the beam.
I almost just did it.
This is definitely faster with a black hole, but those are limited.
That's like the trade-off.
Unless you find a one with like 20 of them.
And you have a speed-up on it and all that.
Then you can go wild.
Can I actually just keep going?
I'm trying to listen.
There's nothing here, is there?
If there's actually something on the right here somewhere, my mind is gonna be blown.
There's just no fucking way, right?
There's no way.
I've made a big tunnel.
This is Minecraft right now.
Get rid of that little piece.
Man, I gotta eat some food as well.
I'm gonna keep digging for a little bit here and then I'm actually gonna go eat some food.
This has been a long stream anyway.
I wonder how many...
So I can't reach out obviously, but I'm just imagining people going, What the fuck is this guy doing right now?
You know?
I don't care.
This is fun, man.
I like digging.
What can I say?
I think I'm going slightly down as I go to the right here.
Maybe I should have put this on a faster recharge.
It is a little slow, isn't it?
I'm also putting this through some heavy use right now.
Am I producing a...
Oh, smoke.
Okay, I thought I was making a...
water vapor...
steam.
But it's actually just smoke.
I'm tempted to go up or down, but I feel like that defeats the purpose of trying one direction, so I'm just gonna try.
I'm gonna stick to the routine here.
I feel like I have been going down a little bit over time, so I may just angle it up just a tiny bit here, to keep things completely straight, sort of.
I can't believe I'm still able to keep going.
Oh!
No way!
What?
Where the f...
What the fuck is this?
What?
That's a sound wave, it looks like.
Dude, I'm getting that pooping feeling now.
The one I told you about.
This is the prime example of something that would trigger that for me.
Oh, that's the bottom.
Why is this...
Where am I?
Why is it so empty?
What the fuck is this?
Oh.
Hello?
Wait.
It goes down.
Hello.
Oh shit!
Huh.
Magical temple?
Why is the...
No, okay, I'm gonna pay attention.
If some text pops up suddenly, I need to pay attention real fast.
Where am I?
I cannot believe I actually arrived somewhere.
This is kind of blowing my mind.
Sup fool?
Oh, you want dance?
Yo, these guys ain't even shit.
Easy peasy.
What does this want?
A self-propelled minecart loaded with explosives.
And there's mana to damage on it.
Only 20 charges on that though.
Wait, what?
Oh, hello.
Oh, these are guys invisible everywhere.
And he's doing that want.
That's not a bad want either.
Sort of.
Oh, I need worm blood.
Hello.
Oh!
He was invisible.
I'm so glad I have light on my want.
Holy crap.
Such a big deal right now.
I need to get the outline of this place and mark it immediately on my map.
Did I hear...
Someone got polymorph just now.
This guy.
Whoa!
Is that... polymorphism?
I can't see what it is.
Okay.
That's kind of dope.
I kind of want to replace that for sure.
Oh, that is chaotic polymorphine.
Let's be real careful with that.
And it goes down here now.
What the...
Oh no, I see that enemy.
That's the worst.
But hold on, they actually don't damage me.
As long as I don't hurt them, we're fine.
Wait, I'm neutralized.
Oh shit.
You're neutralized.
Keep lighting up the place.
Someone's getting polymorphed.
I hear it.
Huh?
Oh shit!
Wizards then.
Wait a minute.
Is that the same place?
Oh, it's gotta be!
It's gotta be.
I ducked like this.
Hold on.
No, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't do that.
I went that way.
Oh!
So wait.
It somehow connects.
Okay, so that's called Wizards then.
I think I missed that last time.
Why didn't I look at the fucking map before I started digging?
Whatever.
Okay, that's good to know though.
Very cool.
Wizards then.
I was getting feelings of I've been here before, you know?
Like I was, I was, I was suspecting that this was the place I was in like last time, but I wouldn't want to...
jump to conclusions.
Whoa!
Huh?
Personal gravity field.
Oh no, we're leaving.
Nope.
We need health.
Also, look at the stone work.
It's changing.
Oh, I don't like this.
We're way too low HP.
We need to heal.
What about all the enemies we killed?
Why are they not bleeding?
Are you not bleeding?
You do bleed.
That's good.
Bleed for me.
Come on.
More bleed.
That's not a lot.
Oh!
We have this spell.
But I can't change my spells on my wands right now.
But that is an option to have.
I should have put that on one of my...
It's basically a healing.
There's a wand there.
Oh, I already tested that.
Wait, did my shield just deflect that wand?
That's sick.
Wow, that could have been really bad.
It's still really bad.
Yeah, you know what?
We're going back from whence we came.
We gotta heal up and take stock.
What the fuck is happening here?
Maybe I want this wand.
Do I want it more than that?
I want this wand.
No, it's only 20 uses, never mind.
Only 20 uses.
Wow, this is easily destroyed too.
Look at this.
I kinda want to try just going up from here.
Is that crazy?
You know what it's crazy?
I need to stop.
I need to eat.
I'm actually... My stomach is hurting.
I've been playing for way too long.
This is a good run, though.
This is a good run.
It's a really good run.
Man.
Today was fun, man.
I got some good runs in.
I'm sorry about the cliffhanger.
I was debating ending this like 30 minutes ago, but...
I was too intrigued by what was happening.
I had to just go a little further, a little further, you know?
You gotta stop at some point, man.
Yeah.
We were very happy that you really realized a little bit of the potential of triggers in this stream.
I feel like I already know potential of triggers.
I've been triggering since day one.
What are you talking about?
I mean, maybe I haven't made amazing things with it, but...
I realized the potential.
At least I think I do.
Going off-road is fun.
Fuck yeah!
I wanna call it that from now on.
That's a good way of putting it.
Going off-road.
Heck yeah, man.
You're so triggering, Oliver.
Nice.
Stay mad.
Just kidding.
Hey, what's up, Lexi?
How you doing?
Mr. Beat, good to see you.
You're gonna watch the VOD?
Have fun with that.
I'm gonna try and put it up ASAP.
When will you stream again?
Probably... let me think.
Probably Sunday or Monday.
Yeah, Sunday or Monday.
I haven't decided yet.
Depends on what's happening.
Statue has some bugs.
Can duplicate projectiles.
Can't really show drill damage.
Okay, that's actually good to know.
Thanks.
Because I thought it was a bug.
I was pretty sure that was a bug, Ducky Bird.
The fact that it only worked on a little, like, pixel of the statue, that was definitely bugged.
So that's actually good to know.
Thanks.
You're doing okay?
I'm glad.
I hope you're having a nice weekend.
I hope everyone is having a nice weekend.
Thanks for streaming.
No problem, Charlie.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for the early pre-upload.
Hey, guys, you don't have to say thanks for that.
Just enjoy.
But I appreciate it.
E .M.D.Meister.
Wie gehtstendir.
I love your approach of blind noiter.
Kinda makes me wish I tried to play this game without any guides at the beginning.
But I find it as exciting to watch you do this as if I did it.
Thanks.
Hey, that's awesome.
I'm glad you're getting enjoyment out of it.
But hey, even if you didn't play it like this...
It's not like I'm trying to make some kind of statement with this at all.
I'm just playing the game I bought, you know?
That's really all I'm doing.
And I don't think there's a wrong way to play a game.
So as long as you had fun, that's all that matters.
This stream was so demon.
I'm glad.
I'm here to provide the demon.
Someday you're gonna see the demon.
I really hope we get to see a demon.
Maybe it's time to use mods to learn wand building?
Nah, the only mods I need is up in my brain.
And maybe they're not very optimal, but they're slowly...
You know, all the weights and biases inside of my brain are very slowly adjusting...
Until the neural network inside of my brain creates amazing wands, okay?
Loving the Prey series?
I'm glad!
Me too!
That game is... I honestly think Prey is one of my favorite games ever now.
That was a really big surprise.
Prey came out of nowhere for me.
Because nobody talks about it!
What the fuck?
And it's like, it's insanely good!
Such a good surprise.
Yeah, it's 80% off right now, along with a bunch of other things.
I actually got a notice on my phone.
There's some other games I wanted to get that are also off.
Do people talk about Noitsa?
Yeah, I would say so.
I've had a lot of people suggest playing Noitsa during my time on YouTube.
But very few people have ever mentioned Prey.
But they did mention Prey at some point, but it was just like, compared to it, far less.
Pacific Drive is also off, yeah.
I've heard that's awesome too.
That's also on my list.
Uh, hold on.
If there's anybody new in the chat.
Here's my list, if you want to check it out.
There's quite a lot of games on there now.
My goal is to play them all.
Isn't that awesome?
Palicado, the wrap-up stream, is gonna happen in the far future, I think.
It's gonna happen at a point in time when I feel like I can't possibly figure out anything on my own anymore.
Or that I'm done with the game, you know?
Which I don't think will happen anytime soon.
But I probably will start playing something else on stream soon.
Uh, but I will come back to Noitsa, I think, regularly.
Just because it's one of those games you get an itch for.
At least I do.
Just wanna play some Noitsa.
Get a run in.
I saw a video saying it's a spiritual successor to Outer Wilds.
I'll have to check.
You know what, speaking of Outer Wilds.
Uh, I was watching, uh, Pirate Software play that.
I'm also watching a bunch of people play Outer Wilds now, of course.
And, man, just, I got some, I listened to that music again, you know?
And I just, I got all those memories back and all those feelings.
God damn.
I have to, I gotta say, Outer Wilds is in my top three games of all time.
It is just one of a kind.
Holy shit.
Yeah, Pirate Software is a streamer.
He is super clever.
It's so entertaining.
I also love his voice.
It's super deep.
And he has, like, a radio voice.
It's super cool.
I've been watching a bunch of, uh, Mapocallops' playthrough as well.
It's a really good one.
You know how people joke about me having dementia?
Here's actually, I saw a video today.
Um, I think, uh, yeah, it was Asmongold talking about how people were criticizing him for not noticing certain things in, I think, Monster Hunter or something.
And I could relate to that so much.
I think when I stream games or when I play games and I talk out loud, I think I get sensory overload from that where I actually will just miss things that I maybe normally wouldn't when I'm just playing.
Because you're using brainpower to talk and say things out loud while you're trying to play the game well and also, I mean, you're having fun with it, you know, and you're being busy.
The game is there.
It's happening.
I think it's making, like, maybe it's just me, but I feel like I get, maybe get sensory overload from that.
And maybe that's why I sometimes completely forget something I was planning on doing just now, you know?
But it could also be a thing about that when everyone plays games, that's how they play games.
They just don't notice it when they're playing it.
But when you have a bunch of people watching it and pointing things out, it makes it seem like you miss a lot of things, you know?
When everyone misses things, it just becomes more apparent when there are people watching.
You're right, Miles.
I also gain things for sure.
Saying things out loud also changes the dynamic completely.
Because when you play games on your own and you don't speak out loud, sometimes you read something and your mind immediately goes somewhere else, you know?
And then maybe that thing is gone.
Like, you don't come back to that thing.
But when you say it out loud, similar to taking notes in class, it's like it sticks better in a way.
So that's why I think I'm much better at keeping track of certain story elements or like names, like just regarding Prey now.
I'm not going to spoil anything, but like bigger things where I have to connect things at the moment, in the moment, is much harder for me.
So in the case of Prey, I would take time in between sessions and compile my notes and be like...
and read some of the stuff that I got during that session where I recorded and be like, oh yeah, fuck, that makes sense.
And then I sort of connect certain things.
You know what I mean?
I don't know if I have ADHD.
I went to a doctor and asked him and he was like, what makes you think you do?
And I said, people on the internet told me.
So he gave me some stuff to fill out, I did.
And I came back and he was like, well, maybe you have?
It's hard to say, it's a hard thing to diagnose based on what you've told me.
And he asked me, well, is it impacting your day to day so much?
And I was like, I don't think so.
And he was like, okay, let's not go further with it then.
So I don't know.
Maybe I do.
Maybe not.
Who knows?
He said that possibly I could have a mild form of it.
I'm honestly not quite sure what he said.
Jokes on you would talk to myself all the time.
Me too.
My dad has been asking me for recommendations for a first game since he wants to know...
Hold on, he's scrolling.
He wants to know more about the medium.
And I'm torn between giving him Outer Wilds or something more accessible.
I would not give him Outer Wilds as a first game, Lexi, because first of all, for non-gamers, just the idea of a first-person game in a 3D world is actually like you wouldn't believe.
Okay, I've tried to... I've watched my dad or my mom play games like that and they don't even know how to look around.
It's not gonna end well for a first game.
You need something more simple for sure if they have no experience.
And I don't know what to recommend, but it's a fun thing to think about, I guess.
What could be a good game to get someone into it?
Okay, guys, I'm actually dying.
I need to eat.
I don't even know how I'm still going.
Thank you so much for watching.
I'm gonna send you off to... I'm gonna... Let's raid a channel.
Someone who's streaming Noitsa, of course.
I think it makes sense to stream someone in the same category.
How about... Let's see here.
Scribbies.
Flashback Fridays.
Or Kaioken.
I have no idea.
I'm just gonna raid someone.
Thanks for watching, guys.
It's a blast.
Thanks for following and all that and checking it out.
Check out the YouTube.
Bye-bye.